url,authorsByline,articleId,clusterId,source,imageUrl,country,language,pubDate,addDate,refreshDate,score,title,description,content,medium,links,labels,matchedAuthors,claim,verdict,keywords,topics,categories,entities,companies,sentiment,summary,translation,locations,reprint,reprintGroupId,places,people,StockSymbol,translatedTitle,translatedDescription
https://metaverseinsider.tech/2022/01/05/nvidia-makes-metaverse-making-omniverse-version-available-free-for-creators-and-artists-worldwide/,Matt Swayne,1e41718707b44b9fb004eb477af046a8,1a45327e68534cc28c6554323888f0fd,"{'domain': 'metaverseinsider.tech', 'location': None}",https://i0.wp.com/metaverseinsider.tech/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Screen-Shot-2022-01-05-at-10.48.21-AM.png,us,en,2022-01-05T15:51:12+00:00,2022-01-05T15:51:12+00:00,2022-01-05T15:51:12+00:00,2.0,NVIDIA Makes Metaverse-making Omniverse Version Free For Creators and Artists Worldwide,"NVIDIA Omniverse, designed to be the foundation that connects virtual worlds, is now available to millions of individual NVIDIA Studio creators","The company made the announcement in a special address at CES. Artists, designers and creators can use Omniverse, NVIDIA’s real-time 3D design collaboration and virtual world simulation platform, to c... [3047 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/omniverse/enterprise/', 'https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/omniverse/', 'https://docs.omniverse.nvidia.com/prod_extensions/prod_extensions/ext_physics.html', 'https://docs.omniverse.nvidia.com/prod_materials-and-rendering/prod_materials-and-rendering/overview.html', 'https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/omniverse/apps/machinima/', 'https://docs.omniverse.nvidia.com/prod_extensions/prod_extensions/ext_aitoybox.html', 'https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/omniverse/apps/audio2face/']",[],"[{'id': None, 'name': 'Matt Swayne'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Omniverse creator', 'weight': 0.10540389}, {'name': 'NVIDIA Omniverse', 'weight': 0.095932305}, {'name': 'Omniverse stages', 'weight': 0.095254414}, {'name': 'Omniverse', 'weight': 0.09364688}, {'name': 'Omniverse Machinima', 'weight': 0.09276104}, {'name': 'Omniverse Audio2Face', 'weight': 0.09251323}, {'name': 'Omniverse Enterprise', 'weight': 0.09047315}, {'name': 'interconnected 3D virtual worlds', 'weight': 0.08364996}, {'name': 'digital 3D nature', 'weight': 0.08316984}, {'name': '3D assets', 'weight': 0.081049226}]","[{'name': 'Metaverse'}, {'name': 'Nvidia'}]",[{'name': 'Tech'}],"[{'data': 'NVIDIA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Omniverse', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'GTC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PlantFactory', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CES', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omniverse', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'RTX', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Nucleus Cloud', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'VUE', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PlantFactory', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PlantCatalog', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Twinbru', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zhelong Xu', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Shanghai', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.09252193, 'negative': 0.012422899, 'neutral': 0.8950551}","NVIDIA has announced that its real-time 3D design collaboration and virtual world simulation platform, Omniverse, is free for artists, designers and creators to use to create 3D assets and scenes from their laptop or workstation. The platform has been in open beta for about a year and has been downloaded by almost 100,000 creators. With Omniverse's core rendering, physics and AI technologies, creators can accelerate their workflows with its core rendering and physics. NVIDIA also reported on new platform developments, including new platform features, such as Nucleus Cloud and 3D marketplaces, as well as ecosystem updates. The company also announced its partnership with e-on software’s VUE, which allows users to create digital 3D nature, from skies and volumetric clouds to terrains, large-scale ecosystems, wind-swept vegetation populations, open water bodies, roads and rocks. Twinbru, a “digital twin of physical fabric” provider, is integrated into Omniverse to help streamline manufacturing and architectural designs.",,[],False,1821406a72e24e97981820daf502464a,[],[],NVDA,,
https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/01/04/nvidia-makes-its-metaverse-building-software-free-for-individual-creators/,Brandy Betz,460e7823dee94d3fa62867bedc7cbf20,045cdf1dbd3540e2858debed12bc6e3c,"{'domain': 'coindesk.com', 'paywall': False, 'location': None}",https://www.coindesk.com/resizer/KulczEjv2lTUnV7Q2Okn8kADryY=/1200x628/center/middle/cloudfront-us-east-1.images.arcpublishing.com/coindesk/YPQHTJZTZRAB3LDU56GJM45MCU.jpg,us,en,2022-01-04T19:35:45.254000+00:00,2022-01-04T19:35:45.254000+00:00,2022-01-04T19:35:45.254000+00:00,2.0,Nvidia Makes Its Metaverse-Building Software Free for Individual Creators,"The tech giant also added new features and partners to Omniverse, its real-time 3D design collaboration and virtual world simulation platform.","At the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas on Tuesday, Nvidia made Omniverse, its real-time 3D design collaboration and virtual world simulation platform, available free to individual creators and ... [1462 symbols]",Article,"['https://venturebeat.com/2021/06/12/nvidia-ceo-jensen-huang-weighs-in-on-the-metaverse-blockchain-chip-shortage-arm-deal-and-competition/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+venturebeat%2FSZYF+%28VentureBeat%29', 'https://consensus.coindesk.com/', 'https://twitter.com/@BrandyBetz', 'https://www.coindesk.com/price/binance-coin/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/price/ethereum/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/price/bitcoin/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/price/aptos/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/price/xrp/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2021/08/03/a-crypto-guide-to-the-metaverse/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/data/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/terms/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/privacy/', 'https://www.coindesk.com/author/brandy-betz/', 'https://consensus.coindesk.com', 'https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2022/01/04/omniverse-available-free-to-creators/']",[],"[{'id': 'd261941771ed4e15abe9638765d119bf', 'name': 'Brandy Betz'}]",,,"[{'name': '3D assets', 'weight': 0.09866749}, {'name': 'Individual Creators', 'weight': 0.09855199}, {'name': 'individual creators', 'weight': 0.09855199}, {'name': 'digital asset libraries', 'weight': 0.09006089}, {'name': 'independent 3D design worlds', 'weight': 0.089851215}, {'name': 'asset libraries', 'weight': 0.088677995}, {'name': 'creators', 'weight': 0.08414062}, {'name': 'video game versions', 'weight': 0.08410078}, {'name': '3D marketplaces', 'weight': 0.083042465}, {'name': 'Nvidia partners', 'weight': 0.08178371}]","[{'name': 'Metaverse'}, {'name': 'Nvidia'}]","[{'name': 'Business'}, {'name': 'Tech'}]","[{'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Omniverse', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Shutterstock', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CGTrader', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sketchfab', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Twinbru', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Consumer Electronics Show', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Computex', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Las Vegas', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omniverse', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nucleus Cloud', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TurboSquid', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jensen Huang', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.14396352, 'negative': 0.010418502, 'neutral': 0.84561795}","At the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas on Tuesday, Nvidia made Omniverse, its real-time 3D design collaboration and virtual world simulation platform, available free to individual creators and artists. The tech giant also rolled out new features and integrations for the product, which the company has dubbed the “metaverse for engineers.” Omniverse combines graphics, artificial intelligence (AI), simulation tools and scalable computing to help designers and creators craft 3D assets and scenes from their laptops or workstations. Nvidia says Omniverse has been downloaded by over 100,000 creators. New features such as the one-click collaboration tool Nucleus Cloud, and new connectors, extensions and asset libraries built by Nvidia partners include 3D marketplaces and digital asset libraries TurboSquid by Shutterstock, CGTrader, Sketchfab and Twinbru.",,[],False,10c0778be0034153a9c1c6c67377d794,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q305177', 'name': 'Jen-Hsun Huang'}]",NVDA,,
https://the-decoder.com/nvidia-omniverse-updates-and-free-version-announced/,Matthias Bastian,a3b58c133d19486f80aa9dfc625d1a69,4577c0e9580b46ec98e8f13a5f680230,"{'domain': 'the-decoder.com', 'location': None}",https://the-decoder.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/NVIDIA-Omniverse-Enterprise.jpg,us,en,2022-01-05T14:43:26+00:00,2022-01-05T14:43:26+00:00,2022-01-05T14:43:26+00:00,2.0,Nvidia Omniverse: Updates and free version announced,"Nvidia's business metaverse ""Omniverse"" comes out of beta and in a free version for more users.","Online journalist Matthias is the co-founder and publisher of THE DECODER. He believes that artificial intelligence will fundamentally change the relationship between humans and computers.

Nvidia’s b... [2652 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.facebook.com/THEDECODERAI/', 'https://www.patreon.com/thedecoder/', 'https://the-decoder.com/tag/nvidia', 'https://twitter.com/TheDecoderEN', 'https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/omniverse/enterprise/', 'https://paypal.me/supportdc', 'https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/omniverse/', 'https://www.reddit.com/r/TheDecoder/', 'https://the-decoder.com/tag/metaverse', 'https://discord.gg/8VKkHAacn8', 'https://www.linkedin.com/company/the-decoder-en/']",[],"[{'id': '5f122db5abb648789b1722a982512d4c', 'name': 'Matthias Bastian'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Nvidia Omniverse', 'weight': 0.10063777}, {'name': 'Omniverse', 'weight': 0.08860201}, {'name': 'Omniverse Audio2Face', 'weight': 0.08689918}, {'name': 'various 3D applications', 'weight': 0.08319751}, {'name': 'other leading 3D software products', 'weight': 0.08056162}, {'name': 'leading 3D marketplaces', 'weight': 0.075094216}, {'name': 'Nvidia’s Omniverse project manager', 'weight': 0.073084265}, {'name': 'New content', 'weight': 0.072105594}, {'name': 'Free digital assets', 'weight': 0.07173881}, {'name': 'free version', 'weight': 0.071034536}]",[{'name': 'Nvidia'}],[],"[{'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'THE DECODER', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Pixar', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Autodesk', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Epic', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omniverse', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 13}, {'data': 'Metaverse', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Unreal Engine', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MetaHuman', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matthias', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Richard Kerris', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Jensen Huang', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CES 2022', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mechwarrior 5', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shadow Warrior 3', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.10705325, 'negative': 0.010335853, 'neutral': 0.8826109}","Nvidia’s business metaverse “Omniverse” (Nuclear) has released a free version of its own version of the Omniverse, which is available to all customers. The goal of the project is to bring together digital work processes across departments and companies, and employees should be able to collaborate digitally in various forms, programs, simulations, and formats via the omniverse. Nvidia also has its own technologies for rendering or physics simulation and the integration of other leading 3D software products such as Autodesk or Unreal Engine. With version 1.0, Nvidia also brings several new features such as updates to Omniverse Audio2Face, an AI-enabled app that animates a 3D face based on an audio track, and new content from Mechwarrior 5 and Shadow Warrior 3 is available in the Omn universe Machinima Library. CEO Jensen Huang said in August that he expects the emergence of a new metaverse economy “bigger than our economy today” and that there will be many opportunities for commerce in these virtual worlds.",,[],False,2b8396a5e7b044a9ae284bd113d163c7,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q305177', 'name': 'Jen-Hsun Huang'}]",NVDA,,
https://beincrypto.com/nvidia-entering-metaverse-race-marketplace-free-software/,Martin Young,f7c12e36e7ba4832896bf18f455885b0,2c5436c0339d47b7a31323849d5b1c08,"{'domain': 'beincrypto.com', 'location': None}",https://s32659.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/shutterstock_nvidia.jpg.optimal.jpg,us,en,2022-01-05T14:00:00+00:00,2022-01-05T14:00:00+00:00,2022-01-05T14:00:00+00:00,2.0,Nvidia Entering Metaverse Race With Marketplace Tie-Ups and Free Software,Microchip giant Nvidia has become the latest mega-corporation to announce its interest in the burgeoning Metaverse ecosystem.,"Microchip giant Nvidia has become the latest mega-corporation to announce its interest in the burgeoning Metaverse ecosystem.

The revelation was made at the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in Las Veg... [2409 symbols]",Article,"['https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2022/01/04/omniverse-available-free-to-creators/', 'https://beincrypto.com/price/bitcoin/', 'https://beincrypto.com/metaverse/', 'https://beincrypto.com/why-is-crypto-market-up-today/', 'https://beincrypto.com/platypus-exploiters-detained-french-police/', 'https://beincrypto.com/yuzo-kano-return-bitflyer-exchange/', 'https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/nvda', 'https://beincrypto.com/news/', 'https://beincrypto.com/cardano-ada-price-prediction-march-bearish/', 'https://beincrypto.com/gary-gensler-everything-bitcoin-accountable-sec-jurisdiction/', 'https://beincrypto.com/facebook-launches-50-million-fund-metaverse-research/', 'https://beincrypto.com/nvidia-crypto-mining-chip-sales-drop-revenue-growth-strong/', 'https://beincrypto.com/markets/', 'https://beincrypto.com/3-biggest-crypto-price-predictions-march-2023/']",[],"[{'id': None, 'name': 'Martin Young'}]",,,"[{'name': 'virtual worlds', 'weight': 0.09517171}, {'name': 'Metaverse marketplaces', 'weight': 0.09390386}, {'name': 'Free Software', 'weight': 0.092022374}, {'name': 'free software', 'weight': 0.092022374}, {'name': 'several Metaverse marketplaces', 'weight': 0.09111609}, {'name': 'graphics hardware', 'weight': 0.081468664}, {'name': 'used graphics cards', 'weight': 0.08143968}, {'name': 'software', 'weight': 0.080427445}, {'name': 'Metaverse projects', 'weight': 0.07893265}, {'name': 'Metaverse Race', 'weight': 0.07636351}]","[{'name': 'Cryptocurrency'}, {'name': 'Metaverse'}, {'name': 'Nvidia'}, {'name': 'UPS'}]","[{'name': 'Finance'}, {'name': 'Tech'}]","[{'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Metaverse', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Omniverse', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Shutterstock', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TurboSquid', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CGTrader', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sketchfab', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Twinbru', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Reallusion', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MarketWatch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Consumer Electronics Show', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CES', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Las Vegas', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Metaverse', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omniverse', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ActorCore', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Daz3D', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PlantCatalog', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'GeForce RTX', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.37301424, 'negative': 0.57401, 'neutral': 0.05297576}","Nuclearchip giant Nvidia has announced that it is entering the Metaverse ecosystem by distributing free software to artists and content creators working on projects and items. The company is already a dominant force in the industry supplying graphics hardware and semiconductors needed to power virtual worlds, and plans to distribute a free version of its Omniverse software for creating virtual worlds. The software is compatible with Nvidia’s top-end graphics hardware, GeForce RTX, and NVIDIA RTX GPUs. Nvidia stock has surged 130% over the past 12 months due to a major supply shortage across the world which has pushed prices sky-high. However, despite this, there are still thriving markets for used graphics cards, with some of which are now fetching more than they cost when they were new.",,[],False,91f2a4b5e45d4370adccfa2ee700d6b7,[],[],NVDA,,
https://www.xrtoday.com/virtual-reality/nividia-reveals-omniverse-free-for-select-users/,Rory Greener,5e30c13dcf824a99b3a9df4b110065ca,67d0938cad9a4e158dda997891e68e8a,"{'domain': 'xrtoday.com', 'location': None}",https://www.xrtoday.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Nividia_Omniverse_Free_Select_Users_New_Tools_Debuted.jpg,us,en,2022-01-06T12:37:35+00:00,2022-01-06T12:37:35+00:00,2022-01-06T12:37:35+00:00,2.0,Nvidia Reveals Omniverse Free for Select Users - XR Today,"XR Today reports on the latest extended reality news from around the globe, including virtual reality, augmented reality and mixed reality.","US tech firm Nvidia announced this week it will make its Omniverse platform available as a free service for all Nvidia Studio users.

Additionally, at this year’s Consumer Electronics Show (CES) 2022 ... [2595 symbols]",Article,"['https://twitter.com/nvidia?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://twitter.com/hashtag/omniverse?src=hash&ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://twitter.com/hashtag/NVIDIAOmniverse?src=hash&ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://twitter.com/hashtag/animation?src=hash&ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://twitter.com/nvidiaomniverse?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://twitter.com/80Level/status/1479004811207004163?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://twitter.com/hashtag/3dart?src=hash&ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://www.xrtoday.com/virtual-reality/geforce-rtx-vr-review/', 'https://www.zdnet.com/article/nvidia-brings-free-omniverse-version-into-ga-unveils-new-nvidia-studio-laptops/', 'https://www.xrtoday.com/virtual-reality/nvidia-omniverse-review-what-is-the-omniverse/', 'https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/studio/', 'https://t.co/7SC53moOnV', 'https://twitter.com/hashtag/nvidia?src=hash&ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://www.xrtoday.com/virtual-reality/the-role-of-the-avatar-in-the-metaverse/', 'https://twitter.com/hashtag/gamedev?src=hash&ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://t.co/eJOa00aVip']",[],"[{'id': None, 'name': 'Rory Greener'}]",,,"[{'name': 'RT3D content creation', 'weight': 0.09385831}, {'name': 'VR content creation', 'weight': 0.093219355}, {'name': 'VR content design', 'weight': 0.09242389}, {'name': 'RT3D design tools', 'weight': 0.08641807}, {'name': 'AI systems', 'weight': 0.07934949}, {'name': 'many new design materials', 'weight': 0.07545233}, {'name': 'Omniverse users', 'weight': 0.07272553}, {'name': 'large RT3D assets', 'weight': 0.07226565}, {'name': 'powerful laptops', 'weight': 0.072029814}, {'name': 'US tech firm Nvidia', 'weight': 0.071459964}]",[{'name': 'Nvidia'}],[],"[{'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 12}, {'data': 'Epic Game’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'GeForce', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omniverse', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'Studio', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Unity', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Unreal Engine', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nucleus Cloud', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Audio2Face', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'MetaHuman Creator', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Canvas', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'GeForce RTX 3080 Ti', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Las Vegas', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nevada', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Consumer Electronics Show (CES)', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.28586248, 'negative': 0.008346309, 'neutral': 0.70579123}","US tech firm Nvidia has announced that its Omniverse platform will be available as a free service for all Nvidia Studio users. At the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) 2022 in Las Vegas, the firm also unveiled various Omniverse updates along with a lineup of new premium and entry-level laptops. The news comes after Nvidia debuted its Omn universe Enterprise in November last year, which optimises the real-time 3D (RT3D) development platform for firms via an upgraded paid subscription service. Nucleus Cloud is a new tool for the Omniverse ecosystem that enables one-click, peer-to-peer file sharing for large RT3D assets and scenes. Users will be soon able to export Audio2Face tool to Epic Game’s MetaHuman Creator 3D avatar development app. Nvidia is also launching a new range of powerful laptops optimised for RT3d content creation, AI-driven development pipelines, and video acceleration more widely available.",,[],False,cb4bdb39140c449da67b7bc9191c8db3,[],[],NVDA,,
https://the-decoder.com/canvas-nvidia-improves-free-ai-painting-software/,Matthias Bastian,26921f421113471089a224cd4fca2377,54ce65883d394bb9b4ff7ba139b0c0f9,"{'domain': 'the-decoder.com', 'location': None}",https://the-decoder.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/nvidia_ki_malen_canvas_gaugan.jpg,us,en,2022-01-06T15:05:35+00:00,2022-01-06T15:05:35+00:00,2022-01-06T15:05:35+00:00,2.0,Canvas: Nvidia improves free AI painting software,Nvidia Canvas supports artists with AI: Simple sketches become full-fledged drawings.,"Online journalist Matthias is the co-founder and publisher of THE DECODER. He believes that artificial intelligence will fundamentally change the relationship between humans and computers.

Nvidia has... [2301 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.facebook.com/THEDECODERAI/', 'https://www.patreon.com/thedecoder/', 'https://the-decoder.com/artificial-intelligence-news/ai-practice/', 'https://twitter.com/TheDecoderEN', 'https://paypal.me/supportdc', 'https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/studio/canvas/', 'https://the-decoder.com/openais-dall-e-2-develops-a-hidden-vocabulary/', 'https://www.reddit.com/r/TheDecoder/', 'https://discord.gg/8VKkHAacn8', 'https://www.linkedin.com/company/the-decoder-en/']",[],"[{'id': '5f122db5abb648789b1722a982512d4c', 'name': 'Matthias Bastian'}]",,,"[{'name': 'landscape images', 'weight': 0.101435624}, {'name': 'white spots', 'weight': 0.0871029}, {'name': 'free AI painting software', 'weight': 0.08330385}, {'name': 'new landscapes', 'weight': 0.0820908}, {'name': 'landscapes', 'weight': 0.0731855}, {'name': 'other graphics', 'weight': 0.069614224}, {'name': 'more drawing ideas', 'weight': 0.06800616}, {'name': 'Nvidia', 'weight': 0.06777659}, {'name': 'different color worlds', 'weight': 0.062104613}, {'name': 'best app', 'weight': 0.060419578}]","[{'name': 'AI'}, {'name': 'Nvidia'}]",[{'name': 'Tech'}],"[{'data': 'Canvas', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'GauGan2', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'RTX', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Windows 10', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Photoshop', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chimera Painter', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'THE DECODER', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Matthias', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Siggraph 2019', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': 'f1d262a1353b4567858f806721fe8cb8', 'name': 'Google Affiliate Network', 'domains': ['google.com'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.074959844, 'negative': 0.016733972, 'neutral': 0.9083062}","Nvidia has updated its free AI painting software, GauGan2: The AI painting tool, GauGAN, with improved backgrounds and four times the resolution. GauGAN was trained with millions of landscape images and learned to compose new landscapes based on the training material. It can also reproduce and automatically add details such as reflections in a still lake or different color worlds according to the season. The beta version of the app is available as a free download and runs on any computer with a current RTX Nvidia graphics card and Windows 10. Google also trained the GAN network with fancy animal creatures instead of landscapes at the Siggraph 2019 computer graphics trade show.",,[],False,8e3411583bb94c119f58a1adb85fc35b,[],[],NVDA,,
https://the-decoder.com/nvidia-and-stanford-show-3d-gan-for-better-fake-images/,Maximilian Schreiner,49b8e76fac4b43ca9ee13077695043ce,21173da9b37e461d898c8cd6f199515a,"{'domain': 'the-decoder.com', 'location': None}",https://the-decoder.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Chan-et-al-EG3D-title.jpg,us,en,2022-01-16T16:27:06+00:00,2022-01-16T16:27:06+00:00,2022-01-16T16:27:06+00:00,2.0,Nvidia and Stanford show 3D GAN for better fake images,"Nvidia and Stanford are showing 3D GANs that can generate even better synthetic images and, for the first time, 3D reconstructions.","Max is managing editor at THE DECODER. As a trained philosopher, he deals with consciousness, AI, and the question of whether machines can really think or just pretend to.

Nvidia and Stanford show 3D... [3599 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.linkedin.com/company/the-decoder-en/', 'https://www.patreon.com/thedecoder/', 'https://discord.gg/8VKkHAacn8', 'https://twitter.com/TheDecoderEN', 'https://www.facebook.com/THEDECODERAI/', 'https://mixed.de/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/EG3D-inversion_compressed.mp4', 'https://www.reddit.com/r/TheDecoder/', 'https://mixed.de/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/EG3D-realtime_compressed.mp4', 'https://matthew-a-chan.github.io/EG3D/', 'https://the-decoder.com/artificial-intelligence-news/ai-research/', 'https://the-decoder.com/stochastic-parrot-or-world-model-how-large-language-models-learn/', 'https://the-decoder.com/tag/nvidia', 'https://paypal.me/supportdc']",[],"[{'id': 'dd647b158ff843fc913509348782bb48', 'name': 'Maximilian Schreiner'}]",,,"[{'name': '3D representations', 'weight': 0.12009449}, {'name': 'Such 3D representations', 'weight': 0.11595825}, {'name': '3D reconstructions', 'weight': 0.09658156}, {'name': 'different angles', 'weight': 0.095928825}, {'name': '3D information', 'weight': 0.09498429}, {'name': 'multiple images', 'weight': 0.093843624}, {'name': '3D GAN', 'weight': 0.09229936}, {'name': 'images', 'weight': 0.09107988}, {'name': 'photorealistic images', 'weight': 0.09073625}, {'name': 'targeted images', 'weight': 0.08993512}]","[{'name': 'Academia'}, {'name': 'Nvidia'}]",[],"[{'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Stanford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'THE DECODER', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'StyleGAN', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'GAN EG3D', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'up to several hours', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.05340734, 'negative': 0.05379994, 'neutral': 0.8927927}","Nuclear and Stanford University have unveiled 3D GANs that can generate even better synthetic images and 3D reconstructions. These 3D representations are used for deepfakes and can also serve as the basis for a 3D model of the person. Nvidia’s StyleGAN variant StyleGAN3 achieved higher stability but is still far away from a natural result, and the team is now demonstrating a hybrid approach (Efficient Geometry-aware 3D Generative Adversarial Networks, EG3D) that combines explicit and implicit representations, making it fast and scaling efficiently with resolution. The team also warns of potential misuse of EG 3D: 3D reconstruction based on a single image and plans to improve their AI there.",,[],False,9f90828ebd3b4537b49798a908418dfe,[],[],NVDA,,
https://the-decoder.com/weekly-recap-meta-vs-ftc-and-a-surprising-comeback/,Matthias Bastian,d27fe5cb8f4f4c62bb0b747dd738f5c3,c5c03da8974c4d118a807337439b518c,"{'domain': 'the-decoder.com', 'location': None}",https://the-decoder.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/mixed_news_der_woche_second_life.jpg,us,en,2022-01-16T16:37:45+00:00,2022-01-16T16:37:45+00:00,2022-01-16T16:37:45+00:00,2.0,Weekly Recap: Meta vs. FTC and a surprising comeback,Flashback to the computer future: The FTC puts pressure on Meta and Apple doesn't get its act together.,"Online journalist Matthias is the co-founder and publisher of THE DECODER. He believes that artificial intelligence will fundamentally change the relationship between humans and computers.

A look bac... [1718 symbols]",Article,"['https://the-decoder.com/artificial-intelligence-news/ai-practice/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/apple-tech-glasses-have-problems-and-come-later-report/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/smart-contact-lense-inwith-first-version-ready-for-this-year/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/tech-giant-tencent-enters-vr-business-report/', 'https://www.facebook.com/THEDECODERAI/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/smart-home-which-devices-support-matter/', 'https://the-decoder.com/sony-camera-photographs-parallel-universes-via-dall-e-2-app/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/meta-ftc-takes-aim-at-vr-strategy/', 'https://the-decoder.com/nvidia-and-stanford-show-3d-gan-for-better-fake-images', 'https://the-decoder.com/truly-intelligent-ai-three-things-googles-ai-chief-says-are-missing', 'https://discord.gg/8VKkHAacn8', 'https://www.reddit.com/r/TheDecoder/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/second-life-off-to-the-metaverse-founder-wants-to-have-another-go/', 'https://www.patreon.com/thedecoder/', 'https://twitter.com/TheDecoderEN', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/does-chewing-gum-help-against-vr-motion-sickness/', 'https://paypal.me/supportdc', 'https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygE01sOhzz0', 'https://www.linkedin.com/company/the-decoder-en/']",[{'name': 'Non-news'}],"[{'id': '5f122db5abb648789b1722a982512d4c', 'name': 'Matthias Bastian'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Meta', 'weight': 0.08653665}, {'name': 'ludicrous speed', 'weight': 0.08462687}, {'name': 'Metaverse', 'weight': 0.08399479}, {'name': 'VR studios', 'weight': 0.07650087}, {'name': 'Second Life founder Philip Rosedale', 'weight': 0.0700854}, {'name': 'WhatsApp', 'weight': 0.06872076}, {'name': 'Apple glasses', 'weight': 0.06793929}, {'name': 'VR', 'weight': 0.06740659}, {'name': 'better fake images', 'weight': 0.066478506}, {'name': 'Supernatural', 'weight': 0.06512057}]",[],[],"[{'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'FTC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'THE DECODER', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NFT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Instagram', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'WhatsApp', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Supernatural', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tencent', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Second Life', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Inwith', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matthias', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mark Zuckerberg', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Philip Rosedale', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Metaverse', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Matter', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'U.S.', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Second Life', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '79ac905d71b74100a0bb06ee94a668ee', 'name': 'Meta Platforms, Inc.', 'domains': ['investor.fb.com'], 'symbols': ['FB', 'FB2A.DE', 'META']}, {'id': 'ef99c73b2c00422e9ac687dd3744c239', 'name': 'Tencent Holdings Limited', 'domains': ['tencent.com'], 'symbols': ['0700.HK', 'NNND.F', 'TCEHY']}, {'id': 'b11c7b94dd624dd28694468bb1f09431', 'name': 'First Trust Large Cap Growth AlphaDEX Fund', 'domains': [], 'symbols': ['FTC']}, {'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.0398463, 'negative': 0.15196535, 'neutral': 0.8081884}","The Daily Discussion looks back on the recent battle between Meta and the U.S. antitrust agency, with a surprising comeback. Mark Zuckerberg is fleeing into the Metaverse at ludicrous speed due to his company's tarnished social media image, a possible breakup of his most valuable platforms, and Apple tightening its advertising thumbscrews. The FTC is launching Meta’s fate negotiations on Instagram and WhatsApp, while the FTC is entering talks with VR studios and blocking the acquisition of the fitness VR app Supernatural. Second Life founder Philip Rosedale is back at his old place of action, and is looking to compete with Metaverse again. Finally, the company Inwith plans to get medical clearance for a tech contact lens this year and launch an initial version in 2022.",,[],False,a0779d803fae4dc989383727747d14b2,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q36215', 'name': 'Mark Zuckerberg'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q1978446', 'name': 'Philip Rosedale'}]",NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/a8893550-fc6c-4301-879d-209aa9323f5b,"Kiran Stacey, Stefania Palma",1a2a0479baa44f06b35122933701263f,20d01f364eed40fa8b8c03ab5e1e8e1f,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F7ddd4dd1-1fa0-4017-8ad4-410ab3846d4b.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-01-18T17:37:51.024000+00:00,2022-01-18T17:37:51.024000+00:00,2022-01-18T17:37:51.024000+00:00,2.0,US to overhaul merger rules in crackdown on ‘unlawful’ deals,Regulators seek public input on guidelines after Joe Biden rails against anti-competitive practices,"The two US competition agencies are to overhaul merger guidelines, which could make it far harder to conclude large mergers and acquisitions as Joe Biden’s administration seeks to crack down on anti-c... [3775 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/6dfdd78a-e229-4524-a400-144396524eb6', 'https://www.ft.com/content/c207e1c4-8978-4482-8b4d-c353acce33d1', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d3726a3a-c4a0-4761-a82c-cda98abc3cb7', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/56a64b704f693a0300dfab7e/subscribe', 'https://www.ft.com/content/e2e34de1-c21b-4963-91e3-12dff5c69ba4', 'https://www.ft.com/content/ba37d061-cd26-47c0-9ff9-1fe8257ee8e2', 'https://www.ft.com/content/fb3396a0-93f6-43b0-ae6b-1ddaab452787', 'https://www.ft.com/content/57cd6686-d1ee-4321-ae35-a8e1fc7f0813', 'https://www.ft.com/content/6fd7d5c3-00b2-43fc-9308-7d96614c53bb', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d03e1302-4091-4b11-a590-1c65358f0ab4']",[],"[{'id': 'a1e3b60824c748098c7b72a54ef7eb8a', 'name': 'Stefania Palma'}, {'id': '68582b7804c04cf89d9cf8f2be6b4e2c', 'name': 'Kiran Stacey'}]",,,"[{'name': 'large mergers', 'weight': 0.07527615}, {'name': 'large deals', 'weight': 0.074052766}, {'name': 'merger guidelines', 'weight': 0.07308077}, {'name': 'many companies', 'weight': 0.0725835}, {'name': 'merger rules', 'weight': 0.07248657}, {'name': 'large companies', 'weight': 0.07235513}, {'name': 'mergers', 'weight': 0.063971005}, {'name': 'anti-competitive practices', 'weight': 0.06341525}, {'name': 'Merger filings', 'weight': 0.062949456}, {'name': 'labour markets', 'weight': 0.062680066}]",[],[{'name': 'Politics'}],"[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Joe Biden’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Jonathan Kanter', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Lina Khan', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sarah Miller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Federal Trade Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Department of Justice', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FTC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SoftBank', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Aon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Willis Towers Watson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Activision Blizzard', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'American Economic Liberties Project', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Just hours', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '1997988fe69d405f9b2ddfbf86625b8b', 'name': 'Willis Towers Watson Public Limited Company', 'domains': ['willistowerswatson.com'], 'symbols': ['0Y4Q.L', 'WLTW', 'WTW']}, {'id': '4de51cf8472b4ce7a5aecdf52a1de4c0', 'name': 'Microsoft Corporation', 'domains': ['microsoft.com'], 'symbols': ['4338.HK', 'MSF.BR', 'MSF.DE', 'MSFT']}, {'id': 'b23d7eae93964df2828ec18ee7f1b34f', 'name': 'Aon plc', 'domains': ['aon.com'], 'symbols': ['AON']}, {'id': '555bf40e1b874ea896086a6841a6a37e', 'name': 'Activision Blizzard Inc', 'domains': ['activisionblizzard.com'], 'symbols': ['AIY.DE']}, {'id': '8287feff45d64b8185dbee81ac8b756e', 'name': 'ARM Holdings', 'domains': ['arm.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': 'd8faa86cf0f64b0aa7d217392c29b4b7', 'name': 'SoftBank Group Corp', 'domains': ['group.softbank'], 'symbols': ['0R15.L']}, {'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': 'b11c7b94dd624dd28694468bb1f09431', 'name': 'First Trust Large Cap Growth AlphaDEX Fund', 'domains': [], 'symbols': ['FTC']}]","{'positive': 0.1001178, 'negative': 0.49884954, 'neutral': 0.40103263}","The Federal Trade Commission and Department of Justice are seeking input from the public on a proposed overhaul of merger guidelines, which could make it harder to conclude large mergers and acquisitions. The move is aimed at strengthening antitrust enforcement amid a surge in tie-ups, and comes as President Biden's administration seeks to crack down on anti-competitive practices. The agencies have focused on the digital economy, asking the public whether there should be different guidelines for deals in this sector, where products and services change rapidly. The public may submit comments until March 21 and the agencies hope to unveil the new rules by the end of the year.",,[],False,0db8daba33ad4c19abc082ca3e9cd48d,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q6279', 'name': 'Joe Biden'}]",NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/eea17031-da02-4b55-ac54-e9453d4c2618,Chris Nuttall,961a70eae45f45298a0be436aad70403,11cc5f08e9df4d89b753a7c68cf5c8d8,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2Fbbfd7bb1-0cc1-47ba-8f93-402a7982c08f.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-01-25T18:55:45.790000+00:00,2022-01-25T18:55:45.790000+00:00,2022-01-25T18:55:45.790000+00:00,2.0,Nvidia falls flat as Arm deal flounders,"Google changes tack on cookies; China to ‘purify’ online content, Muzmatch- Match tiff","Nvidia shares were down as much as 10 per cent on Monday before ending the day flat as part of the Nasdaq rollercoaster ride, but they are off more than 5 per cent today on the company-specific news t... [5216 symbols]",Article,"['https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=5c8b92df81ab3b00044a2110', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d8b0f1de-b4c2-49da-a8ae-a1eacf89394f', 'https://www.ft.com/content/edac3587-33b4-4030-910f-1b4a60348a04', 'https://www.ft.com/content/85b20991-b069-4c4f-a423-a9ea2071471c', 'https://www.ft.com/content/69b0fdac-1f26-4b10-be25-4efa1aadaf09', 'https://www.ft.com/content/3a8d3490-5c8a-4823-a5b9-09f7b02bed65', 'https://www.ft.com/content/235b1af4-4c7f-11e6-8172-e39ecd3b86fc', 'https://www.ft.com/content/3990a256-7d01-4c51-89c1-7973b77a1111', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084/subscribe', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-25/nvidia-is-said-to-quietly-prepare-to-abandon-takeover-of-arm', 'https://www.ft.com/content/285059f7-3f0e-4083-b01f-02e48eccff88', 'https://www.ft.com/content/45cebede-3eb3-4664-b04c-f3b5a416e782', 'https://mictic.com/', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d6cb3541-beef-4335-a0d0-ce5d6585e53d', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084', 'https://www.ft.com/content/ba37d061-cd26-47c0-9ff9-1fe8257ee8e2']",[],"[{'id': '8c8ac6be268b4386a6e3d9a61481b4c9', 'name': 'Chris Nuttall'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Arm deal', 'weight': 0.07389611}, {'name': 'more anti-competitive deals', 'weight': 0.06397576}, {'name': 'chip designer Arm', 'weight': 0.06385658}, {'name': 'Match Group', 'weight': 0.056446232}, {'name': 'Arm Ltd.', 'weight': 0.055977985}, {'name': 'Arm', 'weight': 0.05392082}, {'name': 'SoftBank Group Corp.', 'weight': 0.053918764}, {'name': 'web users', 'weight': 0.05163366}, {'name': 'industry concerns', 'weight': 0.050769657}, {'name': 'online content', 'weight': 0.049764857}]",[{'name': 'Nvidia'}],"[{'name': 'Finance'}, {'name': 'Tech'}]","[{'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bloomberg', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SoftBank Group Corp.', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'the US Federal Trade Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Competition and Markets Authority', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Coinbase', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Justice department’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Activision Blizzard', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Cyberspace Administration of China', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Muzmatch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Match.com', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'OkCupid', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tinder', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hinge', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Moby', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Switzerland', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Capitol Hill', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japanese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Muslim', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swiss', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Latin', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Internet of (Five) Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Floc', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Topics', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jonathan Kanter', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cristina Criddle', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '4efd8787f7df440a9035ac40a01eafef', 'name': 'Match Group, Inc.', 'domains': ['mtch.com'], 'symbols': ['MTCH']}, {'id': '555bf40e1b874ea896086a6841a6a37e', 'name': 'Activision Blizzard Inc', 'domains': ['activisionblizzard.com'], 'symbols': ['AIY.DE']}, {'id': '8287feff45d64b8185dbee81ac8b756e', 'name': 'ARM Holdings', 'domains': ['arm.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': '806457af1fd9418db78388760f52c06f', 'name': 'Alphabet Inc.', 'domains': ['abc.xyz'], 'symbols': ['ABEA.DE', 'ABEC.DE', 'GOOG', 'GOOGL', 'GOOGL.SW']}, {'id': '4de51cf8472b4ce7a5aecdf52a1de4c0', 'name': 'Microsoft Corporation', 'domains': ['microsoft.com'], 'symbols': ['4338.HK', 'MSF.BR', 'MSF.DE', 'MSFT']}]","{'positive': 0.017976915, 'negative': 0.95038, 'neutral': 0.031643037}","Nuclear shares dropped 10% on Monday after news that the deal to buy chip designer Arm may be dead. Regulators in the US, UK, Europe and China would have to give the green light, but there has been mounting opposition to the cash and stock transaction. Google is scrapping the Floc technology it was building to replace advertising cookies, while the US Federal Trade Commission sued to block the deal in order to prevent a chip conglomerate from stifling the innovation pipeline for next-generation technologies. The collapse of the deal would hurt both Nvidia and Arm’s owner SoftBank. The UK launched an investigation into the deal on national security grounds in November after its Competition and Markets Authority expressed “serious competition concerns” in the summer. The US Justice Department’'s antitrust warning has warned that it will seek to block more anti-competitive deals. China has launched a month-long campaign to clean up online content during next week’�s lunar new year festival.",,[],False,d45b2288b6d24a78bebcb64bbf7af35a,[],[],NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/38b56e27-a3d2-4dfb-a3fb-6f3c6aed36a5,George Steer,74d876905f154a09bb85ffc400a0d9fa,671679490d4243389c02b784be1e2a09,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2Faef53ff0-3d40-4546-9d2b-3374e1b5c1a6.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-01-21T05:00:02.157000+00:00,2022-01-21T05:00:02.157000+00:00,2022-01-21T05:00:02.157000+00:00,2.0,Investors turn to Europe in search of stock market bargains,Index of unloved shares has widely outperformed broader global markets in early 2022,"Investors are hunting for bargains in unloved corners of Europe’s equities market as central banks’ plans to unwind their powerful stimulus programmes dull the allure of glitzier tech companies.

MSCI... [3511 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/76bd2194-ccf4-4029-b527-6d56d6c8465c', 'https://www.ft.com/content/8e7e7a4a-140e-4036-b4c7-3423171a597e']",[],"[{'id': None, 'name': 'George Steer'}]",,,"[{'name': 'US stocks', 'weight': 0.093789674}, {'name': 'European value stocks', 'weight': 0.08471812}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.0831664}, {'name': 'Value stocks', 'weight': 0.08193421}, {'name': 'value stocks', 'weight': 0.08193421}, {'name': 'stock market bargains', 'weight': 0.080397025}, {'name': 'European financial stocks', 'weight': 0.07888785}, {'name': 'years', 'weight': 0.07839012}, {'name': 'US', 'weight': 0.073394075}, {'name': 'subdued earnings multiples', 'weight': 0.06730932}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],[{'name': 'Finance'}],"[{'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'MSCI', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FactSet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'GMO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SoFi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Royal Dutch Shell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'HSBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Allianz', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bank of America', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UBS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barclays', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'European', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Jeremy Grantham', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Liz Young', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Emmanuel Cau', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '52f2695ce83640e9827dd1015066d95b', 'name': 'Federal Reserve System', 'domains': ['federalreserve.gov'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '4a361ff3de1545828f9f8a3ba450ceb3', 'name': 'Bank of America Corporation', 'domains': ['bankofamerica.com'], 'symbols': ['BAC', 'BAC-PB', 'BAC-PE', 'BAC-PK', 'BAC-PL', 'BAC-PM', 'BAC-PN', 'BAC-PO', 'BAC-PP', 'BAC-PQ', 'BAC-PS', 'BAC.SW', 'BML-PG', 'BML-PH', 'BML-PJ', 'BML-PL', 'NCB.DE']}, {'id': '84be8c072071419d9a82b30c0c6ab9db', 'name': 'SoFi Weekly Income ETF', 'domains': [], 'symbols': ['TGIF']}, {'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': 'f4b546784b8342188c6e4667c1b410d1', 'name': 'MSCI Inc.', 'domains': ['msci.com'], 'symbols': ['MSCI']}, {'id': 'c38ecb058263496f845c99651c240c68', 'name': 'UBS Group AG', 'domains': ['ubs.com'], 'symbols': ['UBS', 'UBSG.SW']}, {'id': 'daee55bf2049483f98b84c277b7f2f89', 'name': 'BP p.l.c.', 'domains': ['bp.com'], 'symbols': ['BP', 'BP.L', 'BP.SW', 'BPE.DE', 'BPE5.DE']}, {'id': 'e9b84d46761d4396942eb87fdd6468b1', 'name': 'GMO Financial Gate, Inc.', 'domains': ['gmo-fg.com'], 'symbols': ['4051.T']}]","{'positive': 0.4371236, 'negative': 0.51922387, 'neutral': 0.043652516}","Investors are looking for bargains in unloved corners of Europe's equities market as central banks' plans to unwind their powerful stimulus programmes dull the allure of glitzier tech companies.MSCI’s index of value stocks in Europe has jumped almost 5% in the first three weeks of 2022 on a total return basis, far exceeding the nearly 5% decline for the broad World measure of developed market equities. Value stocks have lagged behind as racier but more richly priced, technology shares have flourished. Fast-growing but more speculative US tech shares have sustained particularly heavy selling this year, as investors bet that the Federal Reserve will lift interest rates several times from the historic lows at present. European value stocks have only outperformed the broader global market in two of the years following the global financial crisis in 2008. Funds holding European financial stocks have garnered $1.4bn in new client money so far this year. Analysts at UBS are advising clients to give European shares an “overweight” position in their portfolios relative to the US.",,[],False,6f5213f9442f4e6e8ece62aba5612ab0,[],[],NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/05d218ea-982b-4e95-add1-26550316b2f0,Laurence Fletcher,6ce3509aa0d54dee83b2392fd1533dac,48300e417e6e46509643601ec2880c0b,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F4d59483e-0087-4570-b0cc-1bdefe512fe6.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-01-26T05:00:41.689000+00:00,2022-01-26T05:00:41.689000+00:00,2022-01-26T05:00:41.689000+00:00,2.0,Hedge fund short sellers take aim at green energy stocks,Shares start to fall back after investors sent prices surging to eye-watering levels,"Hedge funds have been cranking up their bets against sustainable energy stocks, wagering that as interest rates rise, investors will be less forgiving of companies with strong environmental credential... [6161 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/10bf413d-cfab-4ace-892b-713e91d759c8', 'https://www.ft.com/content/5fc7031c-d723-40ff-8229-5d90de7bab13', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d26e8ee6-f724-4a7a-8cef-61bd5f101c28', 'https://www.ft.com/content/c5f0e71f-e153-47ac-acc8-c31c2fa2a9b0', 'https://www.ft.com/content/50373787-b9c7-45cd-ab1e-a6c9e5472777', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7775cdec-f2a3-4681-91a4-60cd285c9895', 'https://www.ft.com/content/ccbdd868-5499-11ea-90ad-25e377c0ee1f', 'https://www.ft.com/climate-capital', 'https://www.ft.com/content/ed11c971-be02-47dc-875b-90762b35080e', 'https://www.ft.com/content/b03713d6-5e87-414e-8da3-506163f6497e', 'https://aboutus.ft.com/company/sustainability', 'https://www.ft.com/content/86ecad67-5bea-4ee5-8ad8-a8f28b3112c6', 'https://www.ft.com/content/b4914304-12c5-4fbd-90ba-455d838688d3']",[],"[{'id': '5e7cc6654679409589cbd0760f01ad9a', 'name': 'Laurence Fletcher'}]",,,"[{'name': 'recent years', 'weight': 0.08833626}, {'name': 'hydrogen stocks', 'weight': 0.07627251}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.07560811}, {'name': 'green energy stocks', 'weight': 0.074889354}, {'name': 'green stocks', 'weight': 0.07400097}, {'name': 'sustainable energy stocks', 'weight': 0.07319321}, {'name': 'sustainable stocks', 'weight': 0.07196152}, {'name': 'stock', 'weight': 0.07195469}, {'name': 'stocks', 'weight': 0.07195469}, {'name': 'lossmaking green stocks', 'weight': 0.07127174}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'ESG'}]","[{'name': 'Finance'}, {'name': 'Environment'}]","[{'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Argonaut Capital', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Vestas Wind Systems', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nordex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Breakout Point', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Millennium Management', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AKO Capital', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Financial Times', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Helikon Investments', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Crispin Odey’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'WorldQuant', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'McPhy Energy', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Quantafuel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Soros Fund Management', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Anaconda Invest', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ITM Power', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Enphase Energy', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rivian', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Third Point', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steward Redqueen', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barry Norris', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'James Hanbury', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Renaud Saleur', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Daniel Loeb’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'David Crook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wouter Scheepens', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Danish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Norwegian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'France', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amsterdam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Netherlands', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '35cdc6ca24d04e78b1f6a9f95694c1a5', 'name': 'Quantafuel ASA', 'domains': ['quantafuel.com'], 'symbols': ['QFUEL.OL']}, {'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': 'eb1765a6d7f542188cec289cabf9f22b', 'name': 'Enphase Energy, Inc.', 'domains': ['enphase.com'], 'symbols': ['0QYE.L', 'ENPH']}, {'id': '6f719fb1bf58407f85dcdac08d660bc9', 'name': 'Vestas Wind Systems A/S', 'domains': ['vestas.com'], 'symbols': ['0NMK.L', 'VWDRY', 'VWS.CO', 'VWSB.DE']}, {'id': '0199bc2faae94c17a6433b1219f86a07', 'name': 'Nel ASA', 'domains': ['nelhydrogen.com'], 'symbols': ['D7G.F', 'NEL.OL']}, {'id': '2be45aa56e724b499983097a8747dce5', 'name': 'WorldQuant', 'domains': ['worldquant.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '0b980711c4a943c0a7fc5bc2c11e0d6e', 'name': 'Amazon Pay', 'domains': ['payments.amazon.com', 'textpayme.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': 'eeee660a046242b8bf99f45fdc95cc32', 'name': 'Tesla, Inc.', 'domains': ['tesla.com'], 'symbols': ['TSLA', 'TL0.DE']}, {'id': '375957243b3745d180f46b5de8a3cda7', 'name': 'ITM Power Plc', 'domains': ['itm-power.com'], 'symbols': ['ITM.L']}, {'id': '99eb34289ea0423aa37af4762b9055d6', 'name': 'Rivian Automotive, Inc.', 'domains': ['rivian.com'], 'symbols': ['RIVN']}, {'id': '695ac78882f346db86e93303553665be', 'name': 'Nordex SE', 'domains': ['nordex-online.com'], 'symbols': ['NDX1.DE']}, {'id': 'b9f56e479880470aa9c8a9c35e6f315f', 'name': 'Argonaut Gold Inc.', 'domains': ['argonautgold.com'], 'symbols': ['0UIK.L', 'AR.TO', 'ARNGF']}, {'id': '693b677cd250491bbe284516442874d0', 'name': 'McPhy Energy S.A.', 'domains': ['mcphy.com'], 'symbols': ['0QTF.L', 'MCPHY.PA']}, {'id': 'c5e2f590b3044b59a996374d8e3787b1', 'name': 'Third Point Management', 'domains': ['thirdpoint.com'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.048921026, 'negative': 0.8705399, 'neutral': 0.08053908}","Hedge funds are taking aim at green energy stocks due to rising US interest rates and increased valuations of some of the companies with strong environmental credentials. These companies have seen their shares soar from DKr130 at the start of 2020 to peak briefly above DKr300 a year ago, but have since fallen back. Some hedge funds are betting against these companies, while others are betting on companies whose stories of helping the environment are stronger than their earnings. Higher interest rates mean higher borrowing costs for companies and a lower value ascribed to future cash flows are also a challenge for lossmaking green stocks.",,[],False,a63d0c6c7b8a482382835368594550c7,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q5218659', 'name': 'Daniel S. Loeb'}]",NVDA,,
https://mixed-news.com/en/nvidia-based-cloud-streaming-for-quest-2-plutosphere-launches/,Jan Wöbbeking,2ce82635394b43a4b5051375defb6714,6b22bbb146444018b34204a0f9753c33,"{'domain': 'mixed-news.com', 'location': None}",https://mixed-news.com/en/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/PlutoSphere_VR_Streaming.jpg,us,en,2022-02-04T15:39:18+00:00,2022-02-04T15:39:18+00:00,2022-02-04T15:39:18+00:00,2.0,Nvidia-based Cloud Streaming for Quest (2): PlutoSphere launches,PC VR without a computer: The Nvidia-based streaming service PlutoSphere for Meta Quest (2) offers VR game streaming via the Internet.,"PC VR without a computer: The Nvidia-based streaming service PlutoSphere for Meta Quest (2) offers VR game streaming via the Internet.

Those who do not want to invest in an expensive gaming PC becaus... [3442 symbols]",Article,"['https://uploadvr.com/plutosphere-quest-cloud-streaming/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/virtual-reality-news/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/varjo-now-offers-cloud-streaming-for-high-end-xr/', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/quest-2-pc-vr-a-cult-vr-game-returns/', 'https://sidequestvr.com/app/3247/plutosphere', 'https://mixed-news.com/en/youtube-vr-google-teases-killer-feature/']",[],"[{'id': None, 'name': 'Jan Wöbbeking'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Meta Quest', 'weight': 0.10001493}, {'name': 'Quest', 'weight': 0.09740155}, {'name': 'VR game streaming', 'weight': 0.082244165}, {'name': 'experimental apps', 'weight': 0.07337114}, {'name': 'PlutoSphere', 'weight': 0.07267135}, {'name': 'PC VR apps', 'weight': 0.07243392}, {'name': 'online stores', 'weight': 0.06933228}, {'name': 'stores', 'weight': 0.06899706}, {'name': 'Cloud streaming', 'weight': 0.065371335}, {'name': 'cloud streaming', 'weight': 0.065371335}]",[{'name': 'Nvidia'}],[],"[{'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Amazon Web Services', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SideQuest', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Steam', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Windows', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Epic Games Store', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Rift Store', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AWS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UploadVR', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PlutoSphere', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MIXED', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cloud Streaming for Quest', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'PlutoSphere', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Half-Life', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'WiFi 6', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Pluto-VR', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shadow', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LibreVR', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Revive', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SideQuest', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'VRChat', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'one hour', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Forest Gibson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'VRChat', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Plutosphere', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.036024105, 'negative': 0.0239504, 'neutral': 0.9400255}","PlutSphere for Meta Quest (2) is a Nvidia-based streaming service that streams PC VR apps over the Internet to a Meta Quest. The service is built on Nvidia’s Cloud XR and uses the streaming offering of Amazon Web Services (AWS). It officially launched on February 02 in the SideQuest store and supports both the Quest 2 and the older predecessor model. An Internet connection with at least 50 Mbit download speed and a WiFi 6 router with 5 GHz support are required, but there are no regional restrictions. Steam accounts are mandatory for PlutoSphere, and a token system is used as the payment model. The cost of additional plays varies depending on the bundle selected. Cloud streaming can present latency issues, depending on location and technology, but it does not support Asynchronous Spacewarp. Links to online stores in articles can be so-called affiliate links.",,[],False,e04a00939e914c48947bc1a006bde238,[],[],NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/83f29ea1-d623-495a-8023-91310501393d,"Nicholas Megaw, Naomi Rovnick",04618f6db9ed4042967196aef9f98667,546e0d1ee2284933bd3996f6d5dc05ce,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F69fe5e19-5e1f-4fba-888e-aa1ea884e7df.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-02T08:41:02.938000+00:00,2022-02-02T08:41:02.938000+00:00,2022-02-02T08:41:02.938000+00:00,2.0,US stocks rise for fourth day as traders continue to assess tech earnings,S&P 500 has gained 6% since the start of trading on Friday,"US stocks extended a rally to a fourth day on Wednesday, as strong earnings reports from Alphabet and chipmaker AMD lifted the technology sector after a bruising start to the year.

Wall Street’s benc... [3694 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/5cf5199c-5538-40b6-a059-d2c795108919', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/584573e552860d000491cdb8/subscribe', 'https://www.ft.com/content/ef5ce3b5-f8a6-43ca-9a4d-3a507d12ddab', 'https://www.ft.com/content/41eb5628-79d3-416b-8432-b11fd1ceb905', 'https://www.ft.com/content/bd26296f-2d77-45e3-bc88-9e823e4a4be4', 'https://www.ft.com/content/8e2036b9-c02e-45e8-87d8-c9d3362415f1']",[],"[{'id': '2f55bb3268d541f18215b648912b8b51', 'name': 'Nicholas Megaw'}, {'id': 'da9a1a28c83b4eb9862cca0cfed67082', 'name': 'Naomi Rovnick'}]",,,"[{'name': 'higher interest rates', 'weight': 0.089022964}, {'name': 'rising interest rates', 'weight': 0.086322755}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.08506317}, {'name': 'tech earnings', 'weight': 0.081862934}, {'name': 'overall corporate earnings growth', 'weight': 0.070568904}, {'name': 'high levels', 'weight': 0.06873831}, {'name': 'strong earnings reports', 'weight': 0.06717061}, {'name': 'future earnings', 'weight': 0.06661394}, {'name': 'high operating costs', 'weight': 0.06305839}, {'name': 'fellow tech titans', 'weight': 0.06063568}]",[{'name': 'Markets'}],[{'name': 'Finance'}],"[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'South Korea’s', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'eurozone', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'AMD', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Qualcomm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PayPal', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kospi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'WisdomTree', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'ADP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'San Francisco Fed', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US Treasury', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'European Central Bank', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Asian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'morning', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Aneeka Gupta', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mary Daly', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Christine Lagarde', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '52f2695ce83640e9827dd1015066d95b', 'name': 'Federal Reserve System', 'domains': ['federalreserve.gov'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '0ddb867a9a154995ba037b29840ef17d', 'name': 'The Fed', 'domains': ['the-fed.net'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '4de51cf8472b4ce7a5aecdf52a1de4c0', 'name': 'Microsoft Corporation', 'domains': ['microsoft.com'], 'symbols': ['4338.HK', 'MSF.BR', 'MSF.DE', 'MSFT']}, {'id': '5aa0618f4d7643fba5fb84a93708d4a9', 'name': 'Advanced Micro Devices, Inc.', 'domains': ['amd.com'], 'symbols': ['AMD', 'AMD.DE', 'AMD.SW']}, {'id': '806457af1fd9418db78388760f52c06f', 'name': 'Alphabet Inc.', 'domains': ['abc.xyz'], 'symbols': ['ABEA.DE', 'ABEC.DE', 'GOOG', 'GOOGL', 'GOOGL.SW']}, {'id': 'e3faeff8256e437097fcc315ed8a1977', 'name': 'Águas de Portugal', 'domains': ['adp.pt'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': 'd980f87e11ed436ba2db73fb5a745537', 'name': 'Qualcomm Inc', 'domains': ['qualcomm.com'], 'symbols': ['0QZ3.L']}, {'id': 'a4c7318061e0456391966316124f9f38', 'name': 'PayPal Holdings, Inc.', 'domains': ['paypal.com'], 'symbols': ['2PP.DE', 'PYPL']}, {'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': '5985872d662c4a3f941a9c581a9fce71', 'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'domains': ['apple.com'], 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}, {'id': '9ac0ab6adcf74c9c84ab3fd82038a5d3', 'name': 'European Central Bank', 'domains': ['ecb.europa.eu'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.06248034, 'negative': 0.92353743, 'neutral': 0.013982153}","US stocks rose for the fourth day on Wednesday, as strong earnings reports from Alphabet and AMD lifted the technology sector after a bruising start to the year. The Nasdaq Composite rose 0.5 per cent and the S&P 500 index dropped more than 5 per cent in January due to rising concerns about the effect of higher interest rates, slowing growth and geopolitical tensions. Fast-growing tech businesses had been particularly badly hit by the recent market sell-off, as rising interest rates reduce the value that investors put on future earnings. However, the largest and most profitable companies have remained popular with some investors. Meanwhile, data from payroll processor ADP on Wednesday showed US private sector jobs fell by an unexpected 301,000 in January.",,[],False,3d55fa54d4314ea4afea80a462af1e0d,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q484605', 'name': 'Christine Lagarde'}]",NVDA,,
https://the-decoder.com/nvidia-instant-ngp-ai-graphics-is-on-the-rise/,Maximilian Schreiner,1efd0115048f487cbc7f053e4d691fea,8cf69f39687f49cfb18e0f50dbb2a365,"{'domain': 'the-decoder.com', 'location': None}",https://the-decoder.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Nvidia-Instant-NGP-testbed.jpg,us,en,2022-02-06T15:32:21+00:00,2022-02-06T15:32:21+00:00,2022-02-06T15:32:21+00:00,2.0,Nvidia Instant-NGP: AI graphics is on the rise,Researchers at Nvidia are demonstrating a new AI method to enable the efficient use of artificial intelligence for computer graphics.,"Max is managing editor at THE DECODER. As a trained philosopher, he deals with consciousness, AI, and the question of whether machines can really think or just pretend to.

Researchers at Nvidia demon... [3467 symbols]",Article,"['https://the-decoder.com/ai-graphics-unity-buys-digital-human-startup', 'https://the-decoder.com/stochastic-parrot-or-world-model-how-large-language-models-learn/', 'https://the-decoder.com/nvidia-and-stanford-show-3d-gan-for-better-fake-images', 'https://mixed.de/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Nvidia-Instant-NGP-mueller2022instant.mp4', 'https://mixed.de/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Nvidia-Instant-NGP-nerf_grid_lq.mp4', 'https://mixed.de/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Nvidia-Instant-NGP-teaser.mp4', 'https://www.linkedin.com/company/the-decoder-en/', 'https://nvlabs.github.io/instant-ngp/', 'https://www.reddit.com/r/TheDecoder/', 'https://mixed.de/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Nvidia-Instant-NGP-modsynth.mp4', 'https://paypal.me/supportdc', 'https://discord.gg/8VKkHAacn8', 'https://www.facebook.com/THEDECODERAI/', 'https://twitter.com/TheDecoderEN', 'https://github.com/NVlabs/instant-ngp', 'https://the-decoder.com/deepfakes-are-now-even-more-versatile', 'https://the-decoder.com/artificial-intelligence-news/ai-research/', 'https://www.patreon.com/thedecoder/']",[],"[{'id': 'dd647b158ff843fc913509348782bb48', 'name': 'Maximilian Schreiner'}]",,,"[{'name': 'computer graphics', 'weight': 0.09233676}, {'name': 'many graphics applications', 'weight': 0.0886132}, {'name': 'AI graphics', 'weight': 0.085175894}, {'name': 'neural rendering', 'weight': 0.08015761}, {'name': 'Artificial neural networks', 'weight': 0.07988627}, {'name': 'RTX graphics cards', 'weight': 0.0788319}, {'name': 'neural approaches', 'weight': 0.07439331}, {'name': 'neural volumes', 'weight': 0.07246609}, {'name': 'better fake images', 'weight': 0.06720521}, {'name': 'NeRF training', 'weight': 0.06654146}]","[{'name': 'AI'}, {'name': 'Nvidia'}]",[{'name': 'Tech'}],"[{'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'THE DECODER', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'GitHub', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stanford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SIGGRAPH 2021', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'RTX', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'NeRF-Tex', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'seconds', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'under five minutes', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}]","{'positive': 0.15265284, 'negative': 0.013608379, 'neutral': 0.8337388}","Researchers at Nvidia have developed a new AI method called Instant-NGP, which can learn gigapixel images, SDFs, NeRFs and neural volumes in seconds. This method combines AI upscalers with 3D representations in NeRF's and can create AI-powered global illumination that works with all types of materials and textures. It also learns to predict the paths and ray-tracing effects of path-traced light rays in real time during the rendering process of a scene. The method is so efficient, it can be used in online training and inference, matching the performance of traditional 3D reconstruction techniques. It is available on GitHub.",,[],False,be277b4fd4f04858ac65ec12ced3e43a,[],[],NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/b6309218-c6b7-42b3-b4f4-a66422504312,Chris Nuttall,9d7285fb0c2d4d90b15507e5541bb1a1,d1990e3486814485847ebcf920001deb,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F67816064-c1e0-4f81-b1ab-af1f8263c2d3.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-08T19:24:58.644000+00:00,2022-02-08T19:24:58.644000+00:00,2022-02-08T19:24:58.644000+00:00,2.0,Arm left in Nvidious position,"Peloton board shake-up, Reddit’s ad campaign, Apple’s Tap to Pay","Nvidia’s bid to buy chip designer Arm from SoftBank looked doomed to failure from the outset and its collapse on Monday night has chipped at the hopes, profits and reputations of many.

The graphics c... [4673 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/bf67a94c-5a78-4dcc-aa78-d8ca4557d44a', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084/subscribe', 'https://www.ft.com/manage/subscription/change/da448d11-851d-545c-dc0e-e9a2aef62e54?segmentId=ac1bbcb8-0426-7511-1999-206a41e0c0ae ', 'https://riscv.org/whats-new/2022/02/intel-corporation-makes-deep-investment-in-risc-v-community-to-accelerate-innovation-in-open-computing/', 'https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2022/02/apple-unveils-contactless-payments-via-tap-to-pay-on-iphone/', 'https://www.ft.com/content/3bdbde8d-64b1-40cf-89ba-21b276c192c5', 'https://subs.ft.com/spa3_bc6?segmentId=e6842d0a-6106-4549-7757-1886f543b3ac', 'https://www.ft.com/content/8e1ca412-da98-4a59-9a9b-431e13b0f800', 'https://www.ft.com/content/33c8306c-abad-41f6-874f-e95bb23c6460', 'https://twitter.com/ChrisNuttall/status/1305287367985639424', 'https://www.ft.com/content/59c0d5f9-ed6a-4de6-a997-f25faed58833', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084', 'https://www.ft.com/content/f2fff2a2-5062-4cc6-9814-69c560f39105', 'https://www.pymnts.com/apple/2020/apple-buys-mobeewave-for-100m/', 'https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/bloomberg-got-wrong-apple-wont-kill-square-magic-cube-inc-/', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56b37b064a113e030070f833', 'https://www.ft.com/content/cb2f47ab-429a-4724-b47d-f78c1325d70e', 'https://www.ft.com/content/82774b98-965d-4ed8-9876-cd250ed1448c', 'https://www.ft.com/content/c4c01d86-85f5-49c8-9966-cbf935d834a2', 'https://www.ft.com/content/998c4512-0f12-4bb5-95da-1ca685915fda']",[],"[{'id': '8c8ac6be268b4386a6e3d9a61481b4c9', 'name': 'Chris Nuttall'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Social media platforms', 'weight': 0.061243895}, {'name': 'payment platforms', 'weight': 0.059572157}, {'name': 'activist investors', 'weight': 0.0580298}, {'name': 'Billionaire tech investor', 'weight': 0.057863567}, {'name': 'new marketing deals', 'weight': 0.056082502}, {'name': 'investors', 'weight': 0.053498276}, {'name': 'venture capital company Lightspeed Venture Partners', 'weight': 0.05291951}, {'name': 'Apple Pay', 'weight': 0.052511264}, {'name': 'customers', 'weight': 0.050069924}, {'name': 'app developers', 'weight': 0.049721055}]",[],"[{'name': 'Tech'}, {'name': 'Finance'}, {'name': 'Business'}]","[{'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'SoftBank', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the London Stock Exchange', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Peloton', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Spotify', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Reddit', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'r/WallStreetBets trade', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'WPP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sequoia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Silver Lake', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Alchemy', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lightspeed Venture Partners', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Polygon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Twitter', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FT Magazine', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Instagram', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Stripe', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Shopify', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mobeewave', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Samsung', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Android', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Square', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MagicCube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'night', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japanese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Canadian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Simon Segars', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'John Foley', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barry McCarthy', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Thiel', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Trump', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hannah Murphy', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Risc-V', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tap to Pay', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'iPhone', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Apple Pay', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iOS', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple Watch', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Internet of (Five) Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tap to Pay on iPhone', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '79ac905d71b74100a0bb06ee94a668ee', 'name': 'Meta Platforms, Inc.', 'domains': ['investor.fb.com'], 'symbols': ['FB', 'FB2A.DE', 'META']}, {'id': '53499a692a334d3badd89dc87ed40ff1', 'name': 'Peloton Interactive, Inc.', 'domains': ['onepeloton.com'], 'symbols': ['PTON']}, {'id': '8287feff45d64b8185dbee81ac8b756e', 'name': 'ARM Holdings', 'domains': ['arm.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '2a782b6d6e094287a22238faf2318ffa', 'name': 'Alchemy Resources Limited', 'domains': ['alchemyresources.com.au'], 'symbols': ['ALY.AX']}, {'id': '9f8bc742bdab477fb664f1425b49dacc', 'name': 'WPP plc', 'domains': ['wpp.com'], 'symbols': ['WPP', 'WPP.L']}, {'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': '9c0e5ff08b87453b8f6fa108a73b57b5', 'name': 'Stripe', 'domains': ['stripe.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '0c4a2e2795d046f18a71b8ddbe0de6c9', 'name': 'Shopify Inc.', 'domains': ['shopify.com'], 'symbols': ['0VHA.L', 'SHOP', 'SHOP.TO']}, {'id': '5985872d662c4a3f941a9c581a9fce71', 'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'domains': ['apple.com'], 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}, {'id': '88539c3f7e9d45c9b67bd26c8c3bc1bd', 'name': 'Polygon', 'domains': ['polygon.com'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.020491086, 'negative': 0.8478012, 'neutral': 0.13170776}","Nvidia’s bid to buy chip designer Arm from SoftBank collapsed on Monday night, leaving the graphics chipmaker with a $1.25bn break-up fee to SoftBank. Simon Segars, Arm's CEO, is out and the UK-based company has been weakened by 17 months of strong opposition to the deal from customers who had counted on its designs for the cores of their semiconductors. Risc-V, an alternative, has gained a foothold, with Intel announcing its support this month. Peter Thiel, billionaire tech investor and prominent Trump supporter, will not seek re-election to the board of Facebook's owner Meta later this year. Meanwhile, Reddit is preparing for its own stock market debut by stepping up its push to build an advertising business around the social media platform.",,[],False,02030def611c465480e62e852050f895,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q705525', 'name': 'Peter Thiel'}]",NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/59c0d5f9-ed6a-4de6-a997-f25faed58833,"Antoni Slodkowski, Arash Massoudi, Richard Waters, James Fontanella-Khan",ae28886ea05e46178a49ef9d74ae3b03,0ba14ad94b8947849a979e08e54faf29,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F853f2fad-fb07-4bcb-b7a3-a362f442cfb5.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-07T23:41:39.264000+00:00,2022-02-07T23:41:39.264000+00:00,2022-02-07T23:41:39.264000+00:00,2.0,SoftBank’s $66bn sale of chip group Arm to Nvidia collapses,Transaction had faced scrutiny from regulators and was opposed by rivals,"SoftBank’s $66bn sale of UK-based chip business Arm to Nvidia collapsed late on Monday after regulators in the US, UK and EU raised serious concerns about its effects on competition in the global semi... [3734 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/070f4781-0c9c-4d50-8589-77fde85aae4e', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7033ca79-fcf1-45c0-b6ef-2a57df29277e', 'https://www.ft.com/content/1a13c146-21cb-428a-9771-fcffe9d0023b', 'https://www.ft.com/content/b4649576-9541-4857-b3a4-5b4ccb847642', 'https://www.ft.com/content/8075a9c5-3c43-48a5-b507-5b8f5904f443', 'https://www.ft.com/content/ca7df7d4-7e7e-43b2-85d6-36432d0d9d66', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=58db721900eb6f0004d56a23', 'https://www.ft.com/content/6033ee95-96cd-4c5b-b84a-196bf573f5a7', 'https://www.ft.com/accessibility#video-transcriptions', 'https://www.ft.com/content/cb2f47ab-429a-4724-b47d-f78c1325d70e']",[],"[{'id': 'b52206d4e0284822bc4c3bfe60ddd807', 'name': 'Arash Massoudi'}, {'id': '5804dd46ee024cb79e5158f8ee9b25a9', 'name': 'James Fontanella-Khan'}, {'id': 'c3cf273a175a4ce98c77107d2e76d3e3', 'name': 'Richard Waters'}, {'id': 'd999e626d37b443483ecebec2ebb9a82', 'name': 'Antoni Slodkowski'}]",,,"[{'name': 'chip group Arm', 'weight': 0.091482215}, {'name': 'Arm', 'weight': 0.0903067}, {'name': 'big tech companies', 'weight': 0.08300467}, {'name': 'global tech stocks', 'weight': 0.079060614}, {'name': 'tech stocks', 'weight': 0.07391821}, {'name': 'potential SoftBank stake sales', 'weight': 0.069741696}, {'name': 'Nvidia', 'weight': 0.063312046}, {'name': 'national security considerations', 'weight': 0.061441362}, {'name': 'next fiscal year', 'weight': 0.058884203}, {'name': 'UK-based chip business Arm', 'weight': 0.058527764}]","[{'name': 'Softbank'}, {'name': 'Nvidia'}]","[{'name': 'Business'}, {'name': 'Finance'}]","[{'data': 'SoftBank', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 15}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'Qualcomm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Haas', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Financial Times', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Redex Holdings', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vision Fund', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alibaba', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'EU', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tokyo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hong Kong', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japanese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'British', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Simon Segars', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rene Haas', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Kirk Boodry', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Jensen Huang', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': 'd8faa86cf0f64b0aa7d217392c29b4b7', 'name': 'SoftBank Group Corp', 'domains': ['group.softbank'], 'symbols': ['0R15.L']}, {'id': '2e6aa32adb304b148ae42ed177ca1767', 'name': 'Alibaba Group Holding Limited', 'domains': ['alibabagroup.com'], 'symbols': ['9988.HK', 'AHLA.DE', 'BABA', 'BABA.SW']}, {'id': '8287feff45d64b8185dbee81ac8b756e', 'name': 'ARM Holdings', 'domains': ['arm.com'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.090840526, 'negative': 0.64174026, 'neutral': 0.2674192}","SoftBank's $66bn sale of UK-based chip business Arm to Nvidia collapsed late on Monday after regulators in the US, UK and EU raised serious concerns about its effects on competition in the global semiconductor industry. The Japanese technology group, which will receive a break-up fee of up to $1.25bn, said it would instead seek an initial public offering of Arm before the end of its next fiscal year in March 2023. The deal’s failure brought an immediate management shake-up at Arm, with chief executive Simon Segars replaced by Rene Haas. The collapse of the cash-and-stock transaction robbed SoftBank a windfall from a boom in Nvidia's stock price. Meanwhile, speculation about potential SoftBank stake sales, with its Hong Kong-listed shares falling 2.5 per cent on Tuesday after a 6 per cent drop in US on Monday.",,[],False,4e4dca2ab8274a9aac9f64ecc812c714,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q305177', 'name': 'Jen-Hsun Huang'}]",NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/1e381099-b6ce-4045-a17d-5b390902d494,"Francesca Friday, Joe Rennison, Naomi Rovnick",7e2779eec9b744bb966f89368fbec208,ed6fe27c9f304c5a8f63115c040e6115,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F35a40a96-4bcc-4be4-b223-d90bd6be485d.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-11T08:37:58.626000+00:00,2022-02-11T08:37:58.626000+00:00,2022-02-11T08:37:58.626000+00:00,2.0,Wall Street stocks decline as tension mounts between Russia and Ukraine,S&P 500 falls 1.9% on Friday and is down more than 7% in 2022,"Equities on Wall Street fell on Friday after the US warned that a Russian invasion of Ukraine could come within days and the UK’s Foreign Office urged its citizens to leave the country.

The S&P 500 s... [3932 symbols]",Article,['https://www.ft.com/content/5890811b-3b49-413b-a173-e685a1f4f8e7'],[],"[{'id': '3c0710e4253945ec939bbfdac7ebd11e', 'name': 'Joe Rennison'}, {'id': 'da9a1a28c83b4eb9862cca0cfed67082', 'name': 'Naomi Rovnick'}, {'id': 'fb2e4eb9acd9407f805142bd5063996c', 'name': 'Francesca Friday'}]",,,"[{'name': 'US inflation', 'weight': 0.07113635}, {'name': 'tightening monetary policy', 'weight': 0.067067444}, {'name': 'US', 'weight': 0.063833185}, {'name': 'US consumer prices', 'weight': 0.062694356}, {'name': 'US government debt', 'weight': 0.0625155}, {'name': '0.6 per cent', 'weight': 0.06243588}, {'name': '0.8 per cent', 'weight': 0.06243588}, {'name': '1.9 per cent', 'weight': 0.06243588}, {'name': '1.92 per cent', 'weight': 0.06243588}, {'name': '2 per cent', 'weight': 0.06243588}]","[{'name': 'Markets'}, {'name': 'Russia'}, {'name': 'Russia-Ukraine War'}, {'name': 'Ukraine'}]",[{'name': 'Finance'}],"[{'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Beijing', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'South Korea’s', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'European', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Foreign Office', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brent', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Treasury', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Northrop Grumman', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'L3Harris Technologies', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lockheed Martin', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Edward Jones', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Pimco', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Affirm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jake Sullivan', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mona Mahajan', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Geraldine Sundstrom', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Winter Olympics', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'late-afternoon', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Asia', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '088720f0ac3749baba27b712ee6e209c', 'name': 'Affirm Holdings, Inc.', 'domains': ['affirm.com'], 'symbols': ['AFRM']}, {'id': '8287feff45d64b8185dbee81ac8b756e', 'name': 'ARM Holdings', 'domains': ['arm.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '7ba58a4019cf48afb56c710b0e8d0ef2', 'name': 'Northrop Grumman Corporation', 'domains': ['northropgrumman.com'], 'symbols': ['0K92.L', 'NOC', 'NTH.DE']}, {'id': '5355a853e82a4014b554326668f113dd', 'name': 'Harris Corporation', 'domains': ['l3harris.com'], 'symbols': ['HRS.DE']}, {'id': '2fa32c247a6f4d83be3c163cc685691b', 'name': 'Lockheed Martin Corporation', 'domains': ['lockheedmartin.com'], 'symbols': ['0R3E.L', 'LMT', 'LMT.SW', 'LOM.DE']}, {'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': 'a1d991042d7541a19bb39f469810b588', 'name': 'PIMCO Dynamic Credit and Mortgage Income Fund', 'domains': ['pimco.com'], 'symbols': ['PCI']}, {'id': '0ddb867a9a154995ba037b29840ef17d', 'name': 'The Fed', 'domains': ['the-fed.net'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.023231152, 'negative': 0.960231, 'neutral': 0.016537828}","Wall Street stocks fell on Friday after the US warned that a Russian invasion of Ukraine could come within days and the UK’s Foreign Office urged its citizens to leave the country. The broad US equity barometer is down more than 7 per cent for the year, having hit an all-time high at the turn of 2022. Brent crude, the oil benchmark, rose nearly 4 per cent in late-afternoon trading in New York to $94.96 a barrel, close to its highest point since 2014. Investors flocked to the safety of US government debt, dragging the benchmark 10-year Treasury yield back down below 2 per cent to 1.92 per cent. The broader stock market decline added to losses on Thursday following data that showed US inflation rising at its fastest pace in 40 years, leading investors to price in rapid interest rate rises by the Federal Reserve. European stock markets, with heavier weightings of commodities producers as well as bank stocks, are seen to better weather rate rises.",,[],False,18d5c77a28db4166be7e602eebe19749,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q16730147', 'name': 'Jake Sullivan'}]",NVDA,,
https://www.ft.com/content/b3c2d631-16ef-4ba8-ab18-7cf9450dcd67,,93f790ada95e4c3589e5bd14dc34225a,887a3f48d3334c93a75ce90321cf9c62,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fnext-video-editor-images.s3.ap-northeast-1.amazonaws.com%2Ff5c60bbc-b724-478b-bd22-fb14cca078cc?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-11T05:00:00+00:00,2022-02-11T05:00:00+00:00,2022-02-11T05:00:00+00:00,2.0,Inflation prompts investors to ditch Treasuries,,"A court struggle in China is casting a shadow over the company’s hopes for an Arm IPO after its failed $66bn sale to Nvidia, the 10-year Treasury yield on Thursday climbed to 2 per cent for the first ... [972 symbols]",Article,"['https://acast.com/privacy', 'https://www.ft.com/content/89752c48-753b-4af1-b5e8-03a7cc2f5d27', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7a0213d2-ad59-485f-bcc9-fc0e10a11988', 'https://www.ft.com/content/8494d5f3-4f3e-4a1d-878d-cabb82e37778', 'https://www.ft.com/content/75496422-be4b-48e9-b445-d987813a126f']",[],[],,,"[{'name': 'Arm IPO', 'weight': 0.097746}, {'name': 'US inflation', 'weight': 0.087868966}, {'name': 'Marc Filippino', 'weight': 0.08735246}, {'name': 'renegade China unit', 'weight': 0.08593154}, {'name': 'fastest annual rise', 'weight': 0.08078125}, {'name': 'nuclear fusion', 'weight': 0.07951896}, {'name': 'government debt', 'weight': 0.07763096}, {'name': 'Inflation', 'weight': 0.076209635}, {'name': 'European scientists', 'weight': 0.07452774}, {'name': 'legal battle', 'weight': 0.073952846}]",[{'name': 'Inflation'}],"[{'name': 'Politics'}, {'name': 'Finance'}]","[{'data': 'Treasuries', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Treasury', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SoftBank', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Metaphor Music', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'European', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Fiona Symon', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Marc Filippino', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jess Smith', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Peter Barber', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gavin Kallmann', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Topher Forhecz', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cheryl Brumley', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '94bbd0512cd04cc4b7041d78d9d4cf73', 'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'domains': ['nvidia.com'], 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}, {'id': '8287feff45d64b8185dbee81ac8b756e', 'name': 'ARM Holdings', 'domains': ['arm.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': 'aff4495e1d3d40278d6bb5f9d2a3bd25', 'name': 'FT Cboe Vest U.S. Equity Buffer ETF - February', 'domains': [], 'symbols': ['FFEB']}, {'id': '0a311d1b525e4bfe9d40820a69f05f7d', 'name': 'Franklin Universal Trust', 'domains': ['franklintempleton.com'], 'symbols': ['FT']}, {'id': 'd8faa86cf0f64b0aa7d217392c29b4b7', 'name': 'SoftBank Group Corp', 'domains': ['group.softbank'], 'symbols': ['0R15.L']}, {'id': '07d80b2614ad4030beb11fcaf58866f4', 'name': 'ProShares UltraPro Short 20+ Year Treasury', 'domains': [], 'symbols': ['TTT']}]","{'positive': 0.74390805, 'negative': 0.038814444, 'neutral': 0.21727753}","The FT News Briefing, produced by Fiona Symon and Marc Filippino, reports that the 10-year Treasury yield on Thursday climbed to 2% for the first time since August 2019 due to a court struggle in China. The show's theme song is by Metaphor Music and the FT’s global head of audio is Cheryl Brumley. US inflation surges to 7.5% in fastest annual rise for 40 years, and European scientists have made a big breakthrough in the decades-long effort to generate energy from nuclear fusion. Read a transcript of this episode on FT.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.",,[],False,ab1ffe0d5c4f47c9adb3e79648ef651a,[],[],NVDA,,
https://the-decoder.com/people-dont-recognize-deepfakes-and-trust-them-more/,Matthias Bastian,251e78221b2c4434992b7da3f3c76cc8,f42aebfdf58a4984a9c722ec020831df,"{'domain': 'the-decoder.com', 'location': None}",https://the-decoder.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/fake_bilder_kuenstliche_intelligenz.jpg,us,en,2022-02-15T08:49:17+00:00,2022-02-15T08:49:17+00:00,2022-02-15T08:49:17+00:00,2.0,People don't recognize deepfakes - and trust them more,A study underscores what observers of deepfake technology probably thought anyway: AI-generated photos are almost indistinguishable from real photos.,"Online journalist Matthias is the co-founder and publisher of THE DECODER. He believes that artificial intelligence will fundamentally change the relationship between humans and computers.
