url,authorsByline,articleId,clusterId,source,imageUrl,country,language,pubDate,addDate,refreshDate,score,title,description,content,medium,links,labels,matchedAuthors,claim,verdict,keywords,topics,categories,entities,companies,sentiment,summary,translation,locations,reprint,reprintGroupId,places,people,StockSymbol,translatedTitle,translatedDescription,translatedSummary
https://www.ft.com/content/3f553a29-89af-4d10-af36-dd27b6ab1f38,George Hammond,87a41936930f429fa57f5ce6f2bd0134,177e5ad186be45a7a9071ee5e4937814,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F2ee51958-982e-4f97-8ad8-8fe6a7277575.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-06T19:00:23.567000+00:00,2022-02-06T19:00:23.567000+00:00,2022-02-06T19:00:23.567000+00:00,2.0,Westminster council calls for curbs on Airbnb-style lets,Central London authority wants crackdown on short-term property rentals after complaints from residents,"Westminster council is calling for new powers to curb the use of Airbnb-style rental properties and crack down on rogue landlords who are “making life hell for many of our residents”.

The London coun... [3375 symbols]",Article,['https://www.ft.com/content/c032166d-84fc-407d-b65f-45324123f209'],[],"[{'id': 'f4a7d5d3f229432abf7eca07b15c3936', 'name': 'George Hammond'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Westminster city council', 'weight': 0.1016266}, {'name': 'city centres', 'weight': 0.08476647}, {'name': 'Westminster council', 'weight': 0.08437238}, {'name': 'Other cities', 'weight': 0.08094828}, {'name': 'Many short-term let properties', 'weight': 0.07932485}, {'name': 'council resources', 'weight': 0.07575568}, {'name': 'short-term let rules', 'weight': 0.070139326}, {'name': 'short-term letting antisocial behaviour', 'weight': 0.06915345}, {'name': 'Short-term lets', 'weight': 0.068472356}, {'name': 'short-term let', 'weight': 0.068472356}]",[{'name': 'Airbnb'}],[{'name': 'Politics'}],"[{'data': 'Westminster', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Paris', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amsterdam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Westminster', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ritz', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rachael Robathan', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'William Mews', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Edgware Road', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hyde Park', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '0ac918c3981a4c2f9a93e68f6484f17f', 'name': 'University of Westminster', 'domains': ['westminster.ac.uk'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.011808241, 'negative': 0.8933421, 'neutral': 0.09484972}","Westminster council is calling for new powers to curb the use of Airbnb-style rental properties and crack down on rogue landlords. The London council is urging the UK government to introduce regulations that would allow it and other local authorities to refuse permission to homeowners who wanted to let their properties out for days or weeks at a time. The council also wants people who rent properties through booking platforms, such as Booking.com and Airbnb to be registered, making it easier for the council to track down and fine any landlords who breach short-term let rules. As pandemic restrictions have eased across the country and visitors have returned to the capital, there has been a rise in complaints about late-night parties, overcrowding and even sex work taking place in rental flats. The government is expected to announce a call for evidence into tourist accommodation in the coming weeks, and Westminster will formally submit its proposals then.",,[],False,b06af4ed37694981b2376b3171ba08d2,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/bbabdc53-05f4-4162-bf55-57ae86a70ecd,Dave Lee,254f9806f98346a785c4d87559a32da5,a6645d9e5e2641b881a0c0bb067b48a7,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2Fea9f629d-9701-4d86-8907-342bbb093a00.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-15T22:31:47.325000+00:00,2022-02-15T22:31:47.325000+00:00,2022-02-15T22:31:47.325000+00:00,2.0,"Inflation may push more families to become Airbnb hosts, chief says",Lodging platform touts ‘economic opportunity’ while investors worry about limited supply as travel rebounds,"Rising inflation may drive more families to become Airbnb hosts, its co-founder and chief executive said, as investors raised concerns over limited supply on the lodging platform as demand returns.

A... [3960 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/d42ae8b5-4723-4327-8dd9-13d4b699dbd9', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7a0213d2-ad59-485f-bcc9-fc0e10a11988', 'https://www.ft.com/content/f78399ed-e9bb-4d54-8dbc-b5027ed09965', 'https://www.ft.com/content/208c6a94-f4c3-43e5-8a14-934e5269bcac', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084/subscribe', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d7649340-39be-4aaf-b426-533197627c35', 'https://www.ft.com/content/474516a6-6cbf-4d41-9e0b-62a13754e385', 'https://www.ft.com/content/25d1cf5c-9f20-4861-99d5-a240093fc635']",[],"[{'id': '310a18c06c07480195d9648c643c9bc2', 'name': 'Dave Lee'}]",,,"[{'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.07834252}, {'name': 'Airbnb chief executive Brian Chesky', 'weight': 0.07495227}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07404137}, {'name': 'time', 'weight': 0.07376278}, {'name': 'travel bookings', 'weight': 0.07311288}, {'name': 'Airbnb hosts', 'weight': 0.07306506}, {'name': 'Airbnb', 'weight': 0.06680339}, {'name': 'limited supply', 'weight': 0.06299209}, {'name': 'gross bookings', 'weight': 0.05941627}, {'name': 'total gross bookings value', 'weight': 0.058584645}]","[{'name': 'Airbnb'}, {'name': 'Inflation'}]",[{'name': 'Business'}],"[{'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'American Express', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omicron', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FactSet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Expedia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Booking.com', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Chesky', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'any night', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'nightly', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Covid-19', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Delta', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.9024079, 'negative': 0.05624269, 'neutral': 0.041349437}","Airbnb's co-founder and chief executive Brian Chesky said that rising inflation may drive more families to become Airbnb hosts, as investors raise concerns over limited supply on the lodging platform as demand returns. Airbnb expects bookings to rebound to pre-coronavirus pandemic levels for the first time in the current quarter after concerns about the Omicron coronavirus variant “quickly dissipated” and people become more comfortable travelling. However, the company is still facing challenges in attracting more hosts to join, or rejoin, the platform. The company's recently introduced “I’m flexible” feature has been used for more than 800mn searches for stays since May 2021, directing demand to where supply is more plentiful. Revenue growth at Airbnb, whose business had proved more resilient during the pandemic months than that of its rivals, is now falling behind that of the major hotel groups.",,[],False,eb4d684fba7a43768c30e796cf1970b1,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/16f1bee2-a768-451e-9b59-fad840e6af47,Elaine Moore,9522c44765e54c9e9cb31e92b0290fb2,da1c26785b324637a798835eb231fff2,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F544a13b1-94da-4414-8ff4-5e0c0d99ade4.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-16T12:30:41.883000+00:00,2022-02-16T12:30:41.883000+00:00,2022-02-16T12:30:41.883000+00:00,2.0,The Lex Newsletter: Airbnb’s nomad boss sees future in long-term lets,"With the rise in homeworking, US travel platform aims to tap into the ‘decentralisation of living’",Airbnb founder and billionaire Brian Chesky and I have one thing in common: right now we are both staying in Airbnbs. That is where the comparison ends. My Airbnb is a short-term studio rental in snow... [3749 symbols],Article,"['https://www.ft.com/lex', 'https://twitter.com/bchesky/status/1483474046847225865', 'https://www.ft.com/content/f7512415-46b2-4378-8356-2d1e2a8a760e', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=584573e552860d000491cdb8', 'https://www.ft.com/content/bbabdc53-05f4-4162-bf55-57ae86a70ecd?desktop=true&segmentId=d8d3e364-5197-20eb-17cf-2437841d178a#myft:notification:instant-email:content', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56657d10e4b04e04251004fd', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56b87287f224b50300bf8519']",[],"[{'id': '51f60463b2b44a23b44df2a062cff78f', 'name': 'Elaine Moore'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Airbnb', 'weight': 0.07523548}, {'name': 'gross bookings volume', 'weight': 0.06286744}, {'name': 'pre-pandemic levels', 'weight': 0.06286314}, {'name': 'more professional owners', 'weight': 0.060913123}, {'name': 'new coronavirus variants', 'weight': 0.06088526}, {'name': 'new hosts', 'weight': 0.059814613}, {'name': 'snowy Denver', 'weight': 0.058512896}, {'name': 'travel volumes', 'weight': 0.057735305}, {'name': 'time', 'weight': 0.057648927}, {'name': 'more people', 'weight': 0.057512585}]",[{'name': 'Airbnb'}],[{'name': 'Business'}],"[{'data': 'The Lex Newsletter', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 20}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Booking.com', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Jefferies', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Chesky', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Denver', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Miami', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '7cb761c58f6843c8955d263b8511e8d0', 'name': 'Booking Holdings Inc.', 'domains': ['bookingholdings.com'], 'symbols': ['BKNG', 'BKNG.SW']}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.23191124, 'negative': 0.32161352, 'neutral': 0.4464753}","Airbnb founder and billionaire Brian Chesky is staying in a short-term studio rental in Miami and plans to live in Airbnbs full time. Fourth-quarter earnings released on Tuesday showed gross bookings volume at $11.3bn, up 91 per cent on the previous year and 32 per cent in pre-pandemic 2019. Revenue rose 38 per cent from 2019 to $1.5bn, beating expectations. Airbnb wants to tap into the market by increasing the volume of longer-term stays booked on its platform. However, its market performance has been volatile since listing at the end of 2020, with prices ranging from $135 to $212. It is worth keeping an eye on the success of this strategy as travel volumes tick up.",,[],False,15e2e398146f4a67a2b11c6954b6dda3,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/3196b6c0-ce8e-4874-b4e5-a6266d5424ee,Chris Nuttall,1c18de005ac542189882c9fc811b8588,fcb2d9b50fe245bfab67b0791799caa3,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F6a64fc83-0dff-40e7-bd09-8069c827a590.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-02-16T18:37:38.604000+00:00,2022-02-16T18:37:38.604000+00:00,2022-02-16T18:37:38.604000+00:00,2.0,Becoming best mates with the metaverse,"Android tracking changes, Ericsson may have paid Isis, Google’s smarter canvas","The company formerly known as Facebook renamed its staff “metamates” yesterday, as in shipmates sailing the good ship Social Media into the metaverse.

“Now is the right time to update our values and ... [4755 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/2a7a35b0-104f-4beb-b52e-f45e6e02b4ba', 'https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/workspace/delivering-new-innovations-in-google-workspace-with-smart-canvas', 'https://subs.ft.com/spa3_bc6?segmentId=e6842d0a-6106-4549-7757-1886f543b3ac', 'https://www.ft.com/manage/subscription/change/da448d11-851d-545c-dc0e-e9a2aef62e54?segmentId=ac1bbcb8-0426-7511-1999-206a41e0c0ae ', 'https://www.ft.com/content/14ebaaf6-5b99-4017-b6b0-e8e5878b1f1d', 'https://www.ft.com/content/8779157b-5568-48e7-a117-96b74c6db957', 'https://www.ft.com/content/41b33aa7-7a59-4b50-be47-9911adb34d3e', 'https://www.ft.com/content/bf907e38-ff1f-41c7-b062-529ef238aec4', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56b37b064a113e030070f833', 'https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/disney-names-mike-white-to-lead-metaverse-strategy-1235094281/', 'https://www.ft.com/content/bbabdc53-05f4-4162-bf55-57ae86a70ecd', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084/subscribe', 'https://www.ft.com/content/16f1bee2-a768-451e-9b59-fad840e6af47', 'https://www.ft.com/content/68a4ba34-9785-411c-b7f6-3a9ae2f37cd6', 'https://www.ft.com/content/c23ae405-aca2-4c17-b53d-deaf7c2a595b', 'https://www.coindesk.com/business/2022/02/15/jpmorgan-is-the-first-bank-into-the-metaverse-looks-at-business-opportunities/', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084', 'https://www.havasgroup.com/press_release/havas-group-opens-its-first-virtual-village-in-the-metaverse/', 'https://www.ft.com/content/2422acc5-e618-4d6f-a978-47751e1e869f', 'https://www.jpmorgan.com/content/dam/jpm/treasury-services/documents/opportunities-in-the-metaverse.pdf', 'https://www.facebook.com/zuck/posts/10114316913387601', 'https://play.decentraland.org/?island=Iahlx&position=94%2C21&realm=baldr']",[],"[{'id': '8c8ac6be268b4386a6e3d9a61481b4c9', 'name': 'Chris Nuttall'}]",,,"[{'name': 'individual user behaviour', 'weight': 0.06718631}, {'name': 'user tracking', 'weight': 0.06495205}, {'name': 'more hosts', 'weight': 0.05723003}, {'name': 'users', 'weight': 0.05686593}, {'name': 'capital flight', 'weight': 0.054529898}, {'name': 'gaming addiction', 'weight': 0.053372443}, {'name': 'internet companies', 'weight': 0.052886054}, {'name': 'more families', 'weight': 0.052480362}, {'name': 'new measures', 'weight': 0.0499985}, {'name': 'sweeping new powers', 'weight': 0.049711242}]",[{'name': 'Metaverse'}],[{'name': 'Tech'}],"[{'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Social Media', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'JPMorgan', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Onyx', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Havas', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Group', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walt Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Metaverse Industry Committee', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Android', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Home Office', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bilibili', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'AI2050', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ericsson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Isis', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mark Zuckerberg', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mike White', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Eleanor Olcott', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Chesky', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Schmidt', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Borje Ekholm', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Decentraland', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sandbox', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'metaverse', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Village', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Beijing', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Iraq', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Second Life', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Workspace', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Maps', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Docs', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swedish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': 'e2da5ba5b18d41a3b5af079bfbd3232c', 'name': 'Onyx Acquisition Co. I', 'domains': ['onyxacqu.com'], 'symbols': ['ONYX']}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': '95d490f9ebf140e9920b115be802550a', 'name': 'Bilibili Inc.', 'domains': ['bilibili.com'], 'symbols': ['9626.HK', 'BILI']}, {'id': '806457af1fd9418db78388760f52c06f', 'name': 'Alphabet Inc.', 'domains': ['abc.xyz'], 'symbols': ['ABEA.DE', 'ABEC.DE', 'GOOG', 'GOOGL', 'GOOGL.SW']}, {'id': '92b5b29d8fd64746ada1cfac49719f2e', 'name': 'Telefonaktiebolaget LM Ericsson (publ)', 'domains': ['ericsson.com'], 'symbols': ['ERCB.DE', 'ERCG.DE', 'ERIBR.HE', 'ERIC', 'ERIC-A.ST', 'ERIC-B.ST']}]","{'positive': 0.11959438, 'negative': 0.013067348, 'neutral': 0.8673383}","On Tuesday, JPMorgan and Walt Disney both announced their respective moves into the metaverse, with JPMorgan opening its Onyx lounge in the Decentraland virtual world, Walt Disney appointing an executive to lead its voyage into the new medium. Other companies are also taking advantage of the opportunity to develop their communications strategies for the new world, such as Havas, Disney's first virtual Village, and Google's new measures that will limit user tracking across its Android operating system. Meanwhile, Chinese online video streaming service Bilibili plans to hire 1,000 content censors after the recent death of a 25-year-old staffer sparked heated debate about overwork in the industry. Google is also investing in new features in its smart canvas suite, including automatically generated summaries in its Workspace productivity tools, and Airbnb is posting quarterly profits after losing money in 2020.",,[],False,5ab7c12c271b43f6aa536e81ef2a6308,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q92747', 'name': 'Eric Schmidt'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q1378351', 'name': 'Mike White'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q5629910', 'name': 'Börje Ekholm'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q36215', 'name': 'Mark Zuckerberg'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/ffa67c61-6813-4542-95fe-9d0f8b6cd2a3,Sophia Smith,f3e68091561b479f88ce32db6c20d327,e9635f7809cc463184eea64d1c26580b,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F9caa315d-bc30-4bba-a5fb-2c0802d77919.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-04-06T04:00:32.554000+00:00,2022-04-06T04:00:32.554000+00:00,2022-04-06T04:00:32.554000+00:00,2.0,Are you in on the secret? Why alumni networks are flourishing,"Messaging groups for former co-workers offer support, job opportunities and gossip about former employers","It was a little bit like getting an invite to a secret after-party. When I left my last job, I received an invitation to a Slack channel for former employees. It was as if I’d stood up from my desk, c... [6233 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/8d910754-3568-412c-8a10-9e4806a83b11', 'https://www.ft.com/newsletters', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=62039b7ea31d6577a31f70df']",[{'name': 'Non-news'}],"[{'id': None, 'name': 'Sophia Smith'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Alumni groups', 'weight': 0.0973522}, {'name': 'alumni groups', 'weight': 0.0973522}, {'name': 'official alumni groups', 'weight': 0.09112782}, {'name': 'smaller group chats', 'weight': 0.08077397}, {'name': 'Groups', 'weight': 0.07845578}, {'name': 'alumni networks', 'weight': 0.07658498}, {'name': 'Companies', 'weight': 0.074528456}, {'name': 'companies', 'weight': 0.074528456}, {'name': 'several media companies', 'weight': 0.07244036}, {'name': 'Many companies', 'weight': 0.07131108}]",[],[],"[{'data': 'Slack', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '40 hours', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Slack', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Citi Alumni', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'LinkedIn', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Discord', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Metropark', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Spotify', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Sears', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Telegram', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amanda McQuade', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Fiona Tay', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Fatima Husain', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sara Gunderson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chris', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sophia Smith', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Working It', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.031646818, 'negative': 0.095279105, 'neutral': 0.8730741}","When I left my last job, I received an invitation to a Slack channel for former employees to join alumni groups. To ease the transition, these groups provide an outlet to connect more broadly on industry trends, share resources and sustain the positive aspects of the workplace culture. The Airbnb alumni Slack group, which is over 3,000 members strong, has stringent posting guidelines, with rules prohibiting “derogatory or slanderous” comments against the company. Despite this, some former employees still post in a Facebook group, often sharing Spotify playlists.",,[],False,399df26d75bd4af0a702f5795b78c217,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/7b4a1add-8e5a-4150-9ab4-5b4ab0de3bdf,,ead60c2769844650873d2dc3d27a1c1d,7c59c12ba84a48ea98ae48cf3df7028e,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F13514d16-3f0f-467e-9fd3-3484739be6c8.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-04T00:10:17.269000+00:00,2022-05-04T00:10:17.269000+00:00,2022-05-04T00:10:17.269000+00:00,2.0,Airbnb: remote work leads to booking boom,Room rental company is focused on domestic travel and long-term stays with corporate travel still anaemic,Airbnb’s decision to allow its employees to work from anywhere is not just a way to lure talent. The room rental platform wants users to book increasingly long stays in Airbnb homes. Permitting its wo... [2043 symbols],Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/8bc63067-4f58-4c84-beb1-f516409c9838', 'https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/transportation/business-travel-trends-outlook-2022.html', 'https://www.ft.com/content/bc26db3c-34dd-4ba9-bf0b-2ef422bfd3b6']",[],[],,,"[{'name': 'free cash flow', 'weight': 0.093031436}, {'name': 'impressive free cash flow', 'weight': 0.09016278}, {'name': 'faster revenue growth', 'weight': 0.08536277}, {'name': 'next week', 'weight': 0.080832794}, {'name': 'revenue', 'weight': 0.078383416}, {'name': 'positive net income', 'weight': 0.07355864}, {'name': 'longer stays', 'weight': 0.07319246}, {'name': 'more hosts', 'weight': 0.07130513}, {'name': 'cash', 'weight': 0.06990151}, {'name': 'more money', 'weight': 0.068666495}]",[{'name': 'Airbnb'}],[{'name': 'Tech'}],"[{'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Deloitte', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Covid', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'San Francisco', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Chesky', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jony I', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.78353757, 'negative': 0.06714053, 'neutral': 0.14932188}","Airbnb's decision to allow its employees to work from anywhere is not just a way to lure talent, but it is encouraging users to book increasingly long stays in Airbnb homes. The San Francisco-based company is expected to report its first year of positive net income this year, and its free cash flow has already led to an impressive $1.2bn in the first three months of the year. Prices are already comparable to hotels and longer stays are going to make users more picky. An update to the booking search function will be announced next week, but Airbnb should consider ways to entice more hosts and improve the selection of accommodation on offer.",,[],False,500a6a7b6a904aaba07d5a6815c75570,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/45ac9e5a-5841-4e8e-9ff7-bf2246e43b59,Chris Nuttall,f4a3295400924eb38a727537ba8ef35b,4a488e7bfa5642178aded53f08a4e6d6,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F517f1cc3-c444-4fcc-ac60-f08c73868f36.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-04T17:30:38.047000+00:00,2022-05-04T17:30:38.047000+00:00,2022-05-04T17:30:38.047000+00:00,2.0,Investors drop off Uber and Lyft shares,"US set to target Hikvision, Airbnb’s sunny outlook, Lego builds online business","Ride-hailing rivals Uber and Lyft are on a downhill drive on the stock market after releasing their latest earnings. Uber shares were down 8 per cent at lunchtime in New York on Wednesday, while Lyft’... [4754 symbols]",Article,"['https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/tech/startups/uber-lost-china-but-gained-handsomely-in-didi-global-ipo/articleshow/84017062.cms?from=mdr', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7bc70335-138e-4f56-afe1-ae4383eefb2b', 'https://www.ft.com/content/e2f29ef6-14ae-45c3-b929-b9ac67a4fa75', 'https://www.ft.com/content/809b31e2-6b1e-42b6-8009-3ea78969d870', 'https://www.ft.com/content/0326d115-c124-425f-8b3a-8325d57973a2', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56b37b064a113e030070f833', 'https://www.ft.com/content/191c29da-a68f-4ad4-8892-ef2b5f2bf766', 'https://www.ft.com/content/caa2e8dd-0388-459c-a438-84c0a4cbeb21', 'https://www.ft.com/content/23b8225c-0abe-477a-a26a-21d048b8430d', 'https://www.ft.com/content/923ba655-3967-4ae7-8cf1-b16b4fa75a85', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7b4a1add-8e5a-4150-9ab4-5b4ab0de3bdf']",[],"[{'id': '8c8ac6be268b4386a6e3d9a61481b4c9', 'name': 'Chris Nuttall'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Chinese tech companies', 'weight': 0.08010686}, {'name': 'other companies', 'weight': 0.06770628}, {'name': 'Chinese', 'weight': 0.058207422}, {'name': 'Chinese authorities', 'weight': 0.05768386}, {'name': 'Tom Faber', 'weight': 0.05603596}, {'name': 'human rights abuses', 'weight': 0.05385912}, {'name': 'Chinese ride-hailing company Didi', 'weight': 0.053598266}, {'name': 'the Chinese surveillance camera company', 'weight': 0.051200293}, {'name': 'projected operating earnings', 'weight': 0.049966775}, {'name': 'last June', 'weight': 0.049599767}]","[{'name': 'Lyft'}, {'name': 'Ridesharing'}, {'name': 'Uber'}]","[{'name': 'Finance'}, {'name': 'Tech'}]","[{'data': 'Uber', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Lyft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Didi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'the US Securities and Exchange Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SEC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hang Seng Tech', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Just Eat Takeaway', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Hikvision', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alibaba', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Taobao Deals', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Lego', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Norco', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'lunchtime', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hours', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Hong Kong', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Dara Khosrowshahi', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ryan McMorrow', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Adriaan Nühn', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jörg Gerbig', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Niels Christiansen', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tom Faber', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'William Faulkner', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cormac McCarthy', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Raymond Chandler', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'William Gibson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Danish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Southern Gothic', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kentucky Route Zero', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disco Elysium', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '65beddcdd8c34e12a3ee4ffd81825f39', 'name': 'Uber Technologies, Inc.', 'domains': ['uber.com'], 'symbols': ['UBER', 'UBER.SW']}, {'id': '8df28bcffea74a629159ea5c0d4c6989', 'name': 'Uber Technologies Inc', 'domains': ['uber.com'], 'symbols': ['UT8.DE']}, {'id': 'e08cf07b551b4fd29406a62fd9ba9ca2', 'name': 'Lyft Inc', 'domains': ['lyft.com'], 'symbols': ['LY0.DE']}, {'id': 'd32ed10c29d84233b677f63ba2e3b77d', 'name': 'DiDi Global Inc.', 'domains': ['didiglobal.com'], 'symbols': ['DIDI', 'DIDIY']}, {'id': '3ed712d163c248c88ae99aea936552fc', 'name': 'The Lego Group', 'domains': ['lego.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '2e6aa32adb304b148ae42ed177ca1767', 'name': 'Alibaba Group Holding Limited', 'domains': ['alibabagroup.com'], 'symbols': ['9988.HK', 'AHLA.DE', 'BABA', 'BABA.SW']}, {'id': '670c7a3fcf314925b4df7fd54cac650f', 'name': 'Hangzhou Hikvision Digital Technology Co., Ltd.', 'domains': ['hikvision.com'], 'symbols': ['002415.SZ']}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': '0834d1d8f723478498063036cf691a2e', 'name': 'Norco Performance Bikes', 'domains': ['norco.com'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.009876073, 'negative': 0.97163695, 'neutral': 0.018487006}","Ride-hailing rivals Uber and Lyft have released their latest earnings, with Uber's 8% drop and Lyft's loss of nearly a third of their value. Despite this, Uber's outlook beat expectations and it reported revenue growth of 136% to $6.9bn for the first quarter. Meanwhile, the US Securities and Exchange Commission is now investigating the botched IPO of Chinese ride-hail company Didi, which saw its shares slide 7% in after-hours trading. Just Eat Takeaway's chair Adriaan Nühn bowed to shareholder pressure and agreed to step down, while Airbnb gave a forecast for revenue in the current quarter that easily surpasses Wall Street’s estimates.",,[],False,bfc5cddaf0864b048477b85c3b4272e6,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q29526577', 'name': 'Niels B. Christiansen'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q5221979', 'name': 'Dara Khosrowshahi'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/2c8f5b1e-0b6b-4cf1-9646-41a02bf93da5,Tom Braithwaite,9c33327bffd24a68bc879cee6714834a,02e967abbe844b86953682849f70c4d8,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F1f75c4c7-b2e8-4b8e-bbe8-4c3a5b2784a4.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-06T10:47:58.803000+00:00,2022-05-06T10:47:58.803000+00:00,2022-05-06T10:47:58.803000+00:00,2.0,The recession is coming — and CEOs feel fine,"From bikini waxes to burglar alarms, companies are strangely bullish","Are bikini waxes sticky during a recession? A chain of salons based in Texas, European Wax Center, is confident they are.

Chief executive David Berg told investors this week that he based this optimi... [3496 symbols]",Article,"['https://twitter.com/paulg/status/1301182684811718657?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw', 'https://t.co/wwgf0JvdZ2']",[],"[{'id': '2fbaad0490fb4bc3bd57a6aea2a8510d', 'name': 'Tom Braithwaite'}]",,,"[{'name': 'many other executives', 'weight': 0.08321709}, {'name': 'recessions', 'weight': 0.079412825}, {'name': 'lower growth forecasts', 'weight': 0.076831296}, {'name': 'chief executive Jim Hagedorn', 'weight': 0.0729114}, {'name': 'weaker competitors', 'weight': 0.07262305}, {'name': 'Match Group chief executive Sharmistha Dubey', 'weight': 0.07218258}, {'name': 'Shake Shack chief executive Randy Garutti', 'weight': 0.07184407}, {'name': 'other companies', 'weight': 0.07063435}, {'name': 'executive David Berg', 'weight': 0.06428168}, {'name': 'growth', 'weight': 0.06334996}]",[{'name': 'Business Leaders'}],[{'name': 'Business'}],"[{'data': 'Texas', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ohio', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'European Wax Center', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Covid', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'ScottsMiracle-Gro', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Herbalife', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ADT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Match Group', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chesky', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Shake Shack', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'McDonald’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'David Berg', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Chesky', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jim Hagedorn', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'John DeSimone', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jeffrey Likosar', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sharmistha Dubey', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Randy Garutti', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Great Recession', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '37d4bf076fb84d329360a965a413d41a', 'name': ""McDonald's Corporation"", 'domains': ['corporate.mcdonalds.com'], 'symbols': ['MCD', 'MDO.DE']}, {'id': '557cd8e78f124ce6a6ade139bc2d6733', 'name': 'European Wax Center, Inc.', 'domains': ['waxcenter.com'], 'symbols': ['EWCZ']}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': 'a8d7a8feedc249ed9b662aaabed21f33', 'name': 'Shake Shack Inc.', 'domains': ['shakeshack.com'], 'symbols': ['SHAK']}, {'id': '4efd8787f7df440a9035ac40a01eafef', 'name': 'Match Group, Inc.', 'domains': ['mtch.com'], 'symbols': ['MTCH']}]","{'positive': 0.21315324, 'negative': 0.117951736, 'neutral': 0.668895}","European Wax Center, a chain of salons based in Texas, is confident that its customers are feeling fine during the upcoming recession. Companies that have spent years wanting to be considered as “tech” now emphasise their dull reliability, rather than discretionary, value rather than growth, as well as people who keep buying paint and lawn care items when most home improvement categories fall in a recession. Some companies will perform well during a downturn, weathering the storm and picking up share from weaker competitors. However, other companies require more of a leap of faith. European Wax Center admits it has limited evidence for its recession resilience, but hopes that instead of customers trading up from McDonald's, they might trade down from restaurants.",,[],False,b26fd7ac19714792bb210f1fce17d1d4,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q58494532', 'name': 'Jim Hagedorn'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q16193548', 'name': 'John DeSimone'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/50317b70-2229-450f-9e2a-c41050e59059,Chris Nuttall,ee8aa9b603034c5a83581a7ab2bf4ebf,8a61e5e59124445eb036b30aa84bb31d,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F0de172b6-a6a2-4ab6-9f2e-5135ed571512.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-09T17:49:20.575000+00:00,2022-05-09T17:49:20.575000+00:00,2022-05-09T17:49:20.575000+00:00,2.0,Crypto crumbles as rates rise,"NSO stonewalls, Mukesh Ambani amps ecommerce, Briiv’s tiny forest","While tech stocks are having another dire day, with the Nasdaq Composite index currently down 3 per cent, it’s a double whammy if you’ve also been investing in cryptocurrencies (and bad news for all t... [5549 symbols]",Article,"['https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084', 'https://www.ft.com/content/6691700c-9dfd-4911-8589-70b4ebd2caef', 'https://www.ft.com/content/88e84946-5d75-47eb-8f58-e678f8c326d9', 'https://www.briiv.co.uk/products/briiv', 'https://www.ft.com/content/3f2e4151-743d-48ac-b114-1dbcb7b3f696', 'https://www.ft.com/content/a559cb29-d266-4323-ae2f-96f0d15ff77a', 'https://car.live.ft.com/', 'https://www.ft.com/content/795892b3-806b-4079-8bc9-6cf75dc074f4', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d2a9df43-1ea0-4fb2-9b02-4944589fd909', 'https://www.ft.com/content/3323ae3a-6ace-43f2-a6e5-c0ee9b65b6b9', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7859d08d-c3e0-4531-a01e-510abd6b8284', 'https://www.ft.com/content/bf49236e-0baf-4d53-84d1-563a869aa58d', 'https://www.ft.com/content/304d1447-5fce-421c-9ce7-0d48119da567', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56b37b064a113e030070f833', 'https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-05-09/bitcoin-tumbles-below-33-000-to-lowest-level-since-july-2021', 'https://www.ft.com/content/a97e142b-e718-4cd0-8cfb-aedaaeb3f723']",[],"[{'id': '8c8ac6be268b4386a6e3d9a61481b4c9', 'name': 'Chris Nuttall'}]",,,"[{'name': 'consumer electronics manufacturers', 'weight': 0.066552535}, {'name': 'Taiwanese contract manufacturer Foxconn', 'weight': 0.065872855}, {'name': 'Israeli spyware company NSO Group', 'weight': 0.060482707}, {'name': 'robotics company Addverb', 'weight': 0.058526054}, {'name': 'November last year', 'weight': 0.05745964}, {'name': 'market value', 'weight': 0.055422876}, {'name': 'Foxconn', 'weight': 0.05377554}, {'name': 'Crypto', 'weight': 0.051281746}, {'name': 'crypto', 'weight': 0.051281746}, {'name': 'global financial markets', 'weight': 0.05117106}]",[{'name': 'Cryptocurrency'}],[{'name': 'Finance'}],"[{'data': 'Bali', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'America', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'North Korea', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'EU', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'India', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Scott Chipolina', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Daniel Ives', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Michael Saylor', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mukesh Ambani', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Elaine Moore', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Elon Musk', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Chloe Cornish', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jony I', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jamie Waters', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wedbush Securities', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FT Wiltshire', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MicroStrategy', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Coinbase', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kaiko', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Treasury', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Infineon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NSO', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Berkeley Research Group', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Reliance Industries', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Reliance Retail’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Dunzo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Addverb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Snapchat', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Peloton', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sony', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nintendo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walt Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rivian', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SoftBank', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Foxconn', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Covid', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Micron', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Toshiba', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Briiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Solana', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhone', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Siamese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Israeli', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Indian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japanese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Taiwanese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Future of the Car Summit', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Arctic', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'just an hour', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '2c3d7e5ad5794137b758c59364adddd5', 'name': 'Snap Inc.', 'domains': ['snap.com'], 'symbols': ['1SI.DE', 'SNAP']}, {'id': 'da7e8e8289244e8594a0f837cb1cc51f', 'name': 'NSO Group', 'domains': ['nsogroup.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '0de64ce81893414ca5b3b767c1fd9340', 'name': 'MicroStrategy Incorporated', 'domains': ['microstrategy.com'], 'symbols': ['MSTR']}, {'id': 'de42aeccf8634be2880b74776725a2ab', 'name': 'Nintendo Co Ltd', 'domains': ['nintendo.co.jp'], 'symbols': ['0R1E.L']}, {'id': '92cc610de9324d3e98942e978758be40', 'name': 'Reliance Industries Limited', 'domains': ['ril.com'], 'symbols': ['RELIANCE.NS', 'RIGD.IL']}, {'id': 'b12333acbbe2475e8c687d8d17c5f5d4', 'name': 'Foxconn Technology Co., Ltd.', 'domains': ['foxconntech.com.tw'], 'symbols': ['2354.TW']}, {'id': '99eb34289ea0423aa37af4762b9055d6', 'name': 'Rivian Automotive, Inc.', 'domains': ['rivian.com'], 'symbols': ['RIVN']}, {'id': '98e46d757a3149d29ce4d555b17e37f9', 'name': 'Infineon Technologies AG', 'domains': ['infineon.com'], 'symbols': ['IFNNY', 'IFX.DE', 'IFX.SW']}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': '91b45b2512bd44e8a93b31dd68bcfec1', 'name': 'Walt Disney Co', 'domains': ['thewaltdisneycompany.com'], 'symbols': ['0QZO.L']}, {'id': '05c3bd85a7dd4e499ec46c642bf0a6f4', 'name': 'Micron Technology, Inc.', 'domains': ['micron.com'], 'symbols': ['MTE.DE', 'MU']}, {'id': 'f08426c62eb84b5e80f93b090680fdbf', 'name': 'Sony Group Corporation', 'domains': ['sony.com'], 'symbols': ['6758.T', 'SONY']}, {'id': 'd8faa86cf0f64b0aa7d217392c29b4b7', 'name': 'SoftBank Group Corp', 'domains': ['group.softbank'], 'symbols': ['0R15.L']}, {'id': '0ba4678e268e44f9a9f9deaed07a3ab8', 'name': 'The Walt Disney Company India', 'domains': ['disney.in'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': 'ba9fb2290fae4cd1975c9e5a2b8fd442', 'name': 'Toshiba Corporation', 'domains': ['toshiba.co.jp'], 'symbols': ['0Q0C.L', '6502.T', 'TOSYY']}, {'id': '5b53928f21334f1ca649ae055955c61f', 'name': 'Peloton Technology', 'domains': ['peloton-tech.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '14344799bb5e4342aedbc9cabe80cf3b', 'name': 'Netflix, Inc.', 'domains': ['netflix.com'], 'symbols': ['NFC.DE', 'NFLX']}, {'id': '2069a416008f4285bd8daaaf03071360', 'name': 'Amazon Robotics', 'domains': ['amazonrobotics.com'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.00819362, 'negative': 0.97140783, 'neutral': 0.020398578}","Tech stocks have seen a sharp drop as the Nasdaq Composite index drops 3%, while the top 500 digital assets have also tumbled 50%. Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies have shed $1.6tn in market value since its peak in November last year, and the performance of these coins is tightly linked with the US stock market. Listed shares in crypto-exposed companies have also slumped as well, as well as German chipmakers such as Infineon and Sony. Meanwhile, Disney is expected to post a rise in revenues from its struggling networked fitness company Peloton, while Sony and Nintendo are also looking to sell their 20% stake in Sony.",,[],False,ff7dabacf1554fe0b5db02d3c2845a58,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q317521', 'name': 'Elon Musk'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q6831501', 'name': 'Michael J. Saylor'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/8003a384-bc22-4ae9-b1c1-2c5452136cbe,Emma Jacobs,f0ee49ab48ce40509c5cd8e1e93d5b73,fd4af4584dd7445cb621db11c4315d55,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F19eb879c-5012-4dd5-b8dd-d1dbdc472759.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-09T03:00:34.782000+00:00,2022-05-09T03:00:34.782000+00:00,2022-05-09T03:00:34.782000+00:00,2.0,Why our work trips are starting to look like holidays,The blurring of business travel and leisure — bleisure — is booming in an ‘always-on’ world,"It pains me to say this, but 2022 may finally be the moment for bleisure, the ugly portmanteau describing a cross between business travel and leisure.

I appreciate this makes me sound like I am in th... [4900 symbols]",Article,"['https://twitter.com/bchesky/status/1521582838398820353', 'https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/us/Documents/consumer-business/us-2022-travel-outlook.pdf']",[],"[{'id': 'eccf5395f81848e6b6b69b94a8cb898e', 'name': 'Emma Jacobs'}]",,,"[{'name': 'local Chicago offices', 'weight': 0.07246173}, {'name': 'hotel rooms', 'weight': 0.06934529}, {'name': 'business travel', 'weight': 0.068915926}, {'name': 'office creep', 'weight': 0.06889872}, {'name': 'leisure', 'weight': 0.068113215}, {'name': 'office awaydays', 'weight': 0.06543257}, {'name': 'Work creep', 'weight': 0.06485454}, {'name': 'co-working areas', 'weight': 0.06473346}, {'name': 'office', 'weight': 0.06454791}, {'name': 'staff holidays', 'weight': 0.06324234}]",[],[{'name': 'Travel'}],"[{'data': 'Big Bleisure', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Deloitte', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Hilton', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mews', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '3Thinkrs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Salesforce', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'American Express Global Business Travel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Soho House', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Covid', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'nights', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jason', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Richard Valtr', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Evan Konwiser', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ruth Jones', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chicago', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Amsterdam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Scotts Valley', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'a Trailblazer Ranch', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Working It', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Slack', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': 'eed1d6514e0b4ef1b059ce784d9b7b1b', 'name': 'Hilton Worldwide Holdings Inc.', 'domains': ['hilton.com'], 'symbols': ['0J5I.L', 'HLT']}, {'id': '81508ca5d4aa4c4fb47f09e5c5dfb53c', 'name': 'Salesforce, Inc.', 'domains': ['salesforce.com'], 'symbols': ['CRM', 'CRM.BA', 'FOO.DE']}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': '932cd2db2347407fbda9386cb18307dc', 'name': 'Deloitte', 'domains': ['deloitte.com'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.09862996, 'negative': 0.18633468, 'neutral': 0.7150354}","Business travel and leisure are becoming increasingly popular as the hotel and airline industries look to make up for lost revenues. This is partly due to the fact that workers are more flexible and keen to explore and flexible, and companies are trying to create new sources of income for the business travel sector. Companies such as 3Thinkrs are encouraging employees to collaborate, take part in training and immerse themselves in the company's culture, and group events are encouraging workers to expand their horizons after months of being stuck indoors. The merging of work and leisure is happening at an extraordinary pace, and some employers are helping plan and pay for staff holidays.",,[],False,d1ec042b36ac4c1cbbfe0ce691b109dd,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/278c8e52-9b48-412c-af71-383b8bd60e80,"Alexandra White, Dave Lee",92744bd2d12c4d26ae96f54b804d9ed6,38c3e0b721de47439fb08d508fc4419e,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F4c3bb113-29fa-4d4e-9da8-e32c2806caaf.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-11T13:00:54.171000+00:00,2022-05-11T13:00:54.171000+00:00,2022-05-11T13:00:54.171000+00:00,2.0,Airbnb wants to take tourists to places they never knew existed,Company makes ‘biggest change in a decade’ in effort to ensure peak season is unaffected by supply issues,"Airbnb is revamping its website in an effort to entice tourists to locations where it has more places to stay, as it seeks to ensure pent-up demand during this year’s peak season is not held back by s... [3950 symbols]",Article,[],[],"[{'id': None, 'name': 'Alexandra White'}, {'id': '310a18c06c07480195d9648c643c9bc2', 'name': 'Dave Lee'}]",,,"[{'name': 'more available listings', 'weight': 0.07342701}, {'name': 'more places', 'weight': 0.06870625}, {'name': 'chief executive Brian Chesky', 'weight': 0.0673563}, {'name': 'Brian Chesky', 'weight': 0.064562455}, {'name': 'most people', 'weight': 0.061535828}, {'name': 'Airbnb', 'weight': 0.060245246}, {'name': 'location customisation', 'weight': 0.059494488}, {'name': '30 per cent more nights', 'weight': 0.059490256}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.058492836}, {'name': 'longer stays', 'weight': 0.058075108}]",[{'name': 'Airbnb'}],[{'name': 'Travel'}],"[{'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Tabs', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AirDNA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chesky', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Chesky', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Emily', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Paris', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'France', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'North America', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Arctic Circle', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Asia Pacific', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Split Stay', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'nights', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.7576338, 'negative': 0.017835248, 'neutral': 0.22453097}","Airbnb is revamping its website in an effort to entice tourists to locations where it has more places to stay during this year's peak season. The redesign will introduce 56 different categories, such as “surfing”, “skiing” and “camping’s” as well as characteristics like “houseboats”. It is also adding location customisation, and is playing up its offerings in unusual spots like the Arctic Circle. The company said the upgrade represented the “biggest change to Airbnb in a decade” since going public in December 2020. According to company filings, active listings on the platform have increased by around 7 per cent since the company’�s S-1 filing ahead of the flotation, and the new features will also point people to less well-known cities.",,[],False,84fc5f0671c04aacaaa663c5b60fed85,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/34660eb7-c4cf-48bb-a0d3-fd700e451429,Chris Nuttall,aee97339cc144c4ab7f69e9de1c6f451,8994f404987c40049f1c64f988cdff75,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F4da7f832-5b1f-4d5e-b9e6-f9035401d4e3.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-11T21:35:38.278000+00:00,2022-05-11T21:35:38.278000+00:00,2022-05-11T21:35:38.278000+00:00,2.0,Tesla depends on Lithium-Elon,"Coinbase’s crypto winter, Toshiba’s new suitors, the end for the iPod","Elon Musk saying he would reverse a Twitter ban on Donald Trump provided the main headline from his FT interview at our Future of the Car conference on Tuesday, but Tesla’s incredible progress was the... [4190 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/d1150ebb-9340-422c-8f7b-a52965014fb5', 'https://www.ft.com/content/ab94e730-e83c-11db-b2c3-000b5df10621', 'https://www.ft.com/content/50d2861e-fdeb-487c-b052-f2021558e87d', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d83ec5d8-0ec3-11e0-9ec3-00144feabdc0', 'https://www.apple.com/uk/ipod-touch/', 'https://www.apple.com/uk/newsroom/2022/05/the-music-lives-on/', 'https://www.ft.com/content/87fa2879-c2ab-4efb-892d-edfc0b30154c', 'https://www.ft.com/content/87e5eff2-ff1a-4d46-93e0-5b9f889d00df', 'https://www.fastcompany.com/90750815/ipod-touch-discontinued', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7587d510-894a-4b1c-8923-b9711e3ce4d1', 'https://www.ft.com/content/dd6f2dd0-1dad-4747-8ca4-cb63b026a757', 'https://www.ft.com/content/53697164-cfd0-4a73-add4-9628b5c4c273', 'https://pocketnow.com/how-apple-ipod-changed-world', 'https://www.ft.com/content/5f2e4079-3e4e-4515-ad6b-649d2da25012', 'https://www.ft.com/content/278c8e52-9b48-412c-af71-383b8bd60e80', 'https://www.ft.com/content/2bf4e8db-e35c-40fd-9fdc-bfff6745e90f', 'https://www.ft.com/content/50c1e24d-4b28-42fe-bb29-e9d13aa01909', 'https://www.ft.com/content/e7b1ecc5-1070-47be-be2c-f1549624068c', 'https://www.ft.com/content/343153a1-87fe-4221-afaf-151b9d271590', 'https://car.live.ft.com/home', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56b37b064a113e030070f833']",[],"[{'id': '8c8ac6be268b4386a6e3d9a61481b4c9', 'name': 'Chris Nuttall'}]",,,"[{'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.064322375}, {'name': 'supply issues', 'weight': 0.054953396}, {'name': 'soccer partnership', 'weight': 0.053050973}, {'name': 'peak demand', 'weight': 0.0529567}, {'name': 'trading volumes', 'weight': 0.05204108}, {'name': 'cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase', 'weight': 0.050016135}, {'name': 'early days', 'weight': 0.049981225}, {'name': 'private equity group KKR', 'weight': 0.047333226}, {'name': 'Coinbase chief', 'weight': 0.04603153}, {'name': 'Toshiba', 'weight': 0.044936072}]",[{'name': 'Tesla'}],[{'name': 'Auto'}],"[{'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'FT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Future of the Car', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Twitter', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Coinbase', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Sea', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Affirm', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Toshiba', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'KKR', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Blackstone', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Bain Capital', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Fifa', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Electronic Arts', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'EA Sports FC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Apple Store', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Pocketnow', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Elon Musk', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Donald Trump', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Richard Waters', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Brian Armstrong', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Harry McCracken', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lotus', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Elise', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPod', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'iPhone', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Highway 101', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Thailand', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Indonesia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Asia', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': 'b38369085a7a44c0a9eff5ad07eb8730', 'name': 'Sea Limited', 'domains': ['sea.com'], 'symbols': ['SE']}, {'id': 'eeee660a046242b8bf99f45fdc95cc32', 'name': 'Tesla, Inc.', 'domains': ['tesla.com'], 'symbols': ['TSLA', 'TL0.DE']}, {'id': 'ba9fb2290fae4cd1975c9e5a2b8fd442', 'name': 'Toshiba Corporation', 'domains': ['toshiba.co.jp'], 'symbols': ['0Q0C.L', '6502.T', 'TOSYY']}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': '6ce1e5d716e3473089e58e8a2b4e8883', 'name': 'Electronic Arts Inc.', 'domains': ['ea.com'], 'symbols': ['0IFX.L', 'EA']}, {'id': 'a55cdf3bff434f6fa45555676da8762f', 'name': 'Electronic Arts Inc', 'domains': ['ea.com'], 'symbols': ['ERT.DE']}, {'id': 'ac8db23b44fe41a38035fdad118e773b', 'name': 'Toshiba Tec Corporation', 'domains': ['toshibatec.com'], 'symbols': ['6588.T']}]","{'positive': 0.021232268, 'negative': 0.9314776, 'neutral': 0.047290217}","Elon Musk said he would reverse a Twitter ban on Donald Trump at the Future of the Car conference on Tuesday, but Tesla's incredible progress was the big subject of discussion. Musk said Tesla was getting everything wrong at the time, and that lithium-ion batteries were a big challenge. The US is aiming to expand mining of the metal, with demand for it expected to far outstrip supply. Airbnb is revamping its website in an effort to entice tourists to locations where it has more places to stay, and EA is ending a 30-year partnership with Fifa.",,[],False,6b302f19881f4e6496ea546a9fe07f6c,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q22686', 'name': 'Donald Trump'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q317521', 'name': 'Elon Musk'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q64705310', 'name': 'Brian Armstrong'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/f491744b-10a9-4f0a-b4b5-d9d8851aff24,"Dave Lee, Ryan McMorrow",f922677c756144a9a5041f9599144bcc,5152cbac95ad475396a9fe67b9dd1c1f,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2Ff39a70f4-29d4-4cb1-afd0-43624d1b149d.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-23T21:46:31.830000+00:00,2022-05-23T21:46:31.830000+00:00,2022-05-23T21:46:31.830000+00:00,2.0,Airbnb gives up on China as zero-Covid policy crushes tourism,Rental company abandons push to compete in local market and shifts focus to overseas trips,"Airbnb will close its China business this summer after a years-long push to crack the market was throttled by the impact of Beijing’s harsh zero-Covid strategy on domestic and international tourism.

... [3973 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/stream/19d68630-721b-4153-8280-c8f4e7895cdc', 'https://www.ft.com/content/1e5bacc2-0e98-11e7-b030-768954394623', 'https://www.ft.com/content/f2fa28da-ef50-41c8-aadf-0a384f9ee47f', 'https://www.ft.com/content/69ac0449-c6f9-4b30-a346-bd6716e735e5', 'https://www.ft.com/content/b91c64e9-d67c-46e7-8923-69de55f5c38b']",[],"[{'id': '73fb55ca5c0f49efa2cc196b1bd1eca0', 'name': 'Ryan Mcmorrow'}, {'id': '310a18c06c07480195d9648c643c9bc2', 'name': 'Dave Lee'}]",,,"[{'name': 'Airbnb China', 'weight': 0.10842091}, {'name': 'Airbnb', 'weight': 0.08269031}, {'name': 'China', 'weight': 0.07991741}, {'name': 'mainland China', 'weight': 0.07932872}, {'name': 'outbound Chinese tourists', 'weight': 0.0786085}, {'name': 'Larger domestic travel booking platforms', 'weight': 0.07553802}, {'name': 'Chinese tourists', 'weight': 0.07195613}, {'name': 'outbound travel', 'weight': 0.07111192}, {'name': 'Chinese authorities', 'weight': 0.06881279}, {'name': 'Airbnb’s China business', 'weight': 0.064651005}]","[{'name': 'Airbnb'}, {'name': 'China'}, {'name': 'Coronavirus'}]",[{'name': 'Travel'}],"[{'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 19}, {'data': 'WeChat', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tujia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Xiaozhu', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UN', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'World Tourism Organization', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'University of Queensland', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ctrip', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'FBI', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'CNBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LinkedIn', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Uber', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Didi Chuxing', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 12}, {'data': 'Beijing', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Nathan Blecharczyk', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Xie', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sean Joyce', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vivian Wu', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Americans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.0131827565, 'negative': 0.95165884, 'neutral': 0.03515851}","Airbnb has announced that it will close its domestic travel and experience listings in China by the end of July due to the impact of Beijing's harsh zero-Covid strategy on domestic and international tourism. Bookings from foreigners travelling into China have accounted for about 1 per cent of Airbnb’s overall revenue, while larger domestic travel booking platforms such as Ctrip have also pushed into the home rental segment. Airbnb's presence in China had also been the source of controversy, with former FBI deputy director Sean Joyce resigning in 2020 due to concerns about data-sharing.",,"[{'country': 'mx', 'state': 'NLE', 'county': 'China'}]",False,7569f37be5374855b733a1223da1bfb0,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q464754', 'name': 'Vivian Wu'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q19538950', 'name': 'Nathan Blecharczyk'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/1041fb0a-2688-4809-a3a1-b721b48a9040,Chris Nuttall,ad1d12da837d4f439f7b3fec2f512f6d,f19f883df9084b8ea89b7cfa91ec4646,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F37f8a7a3-e65e-417a-9d39-20947ff294c6.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-24T17:09:26.873000+00:00,2022-05-24T17:09:26.873000+00:00,2022-05-24T17:09:26.873000+00:00,2.0,Snap breaks bad news on ads,"Airbnb’s China retreat, Digital nomad-eira, Logitech’s MX Mechanical","Things are going south fast for social media, with Snap warning overnight of a rapid deterioration over the past month in the “macroeconomic environment”, leading to its shares falling more than 40 pe... [5039 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/231c6d32-11bd-4035-84e1-14d93417941a', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56703b20cb56e617eb2c4084', 'https://www.ft.com/content/12cbf9db-cfff-4593-82e0-4191436f3c2a', 'https://www.ft.com/content/2b8d6fa1-cae8-4e29-9953-834a43a0fd29', 'https://www.ft.com/content/ed185cbf-6394-4444-9f8b-121c1bca808a#post-0bf20d44-3c8d-4325-9e14-f65df2b75df0', 'https://www.ft.com/content/b9164afa-0968-4527-a7f1-5cd616699fa6', 'https://www.ft.com/content/d4a79791-cc8b-4c51-9515-f004e3d5b50e', 'https://www.canalys.com/newsroom/european-smartphone-market-Q1-2022?ctid=2744-66714f963b07b072b94cf626e6aa3628', 'https://www.logitech.com/en-gb/products/keyboards/mx-mechanical.html', 'https://www.ft.com/content/f491744b-10a9-4f0a-b4b5-d9d8851aff24', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/subscribe?newsletterIds=56b37b064a113e030070f833', 'https://www.ft.com/content/3a561a90-b77d-4b9f-a2bd-7587b2b12aa6', 'https://www.logitech.com/en-gb/products/mice/mx-master-3s.910-006559.html', 'https://www.ft.com/content/f2fa28da-ef50-41c8-aadf-0a384f9ee47f', 'https://www.ft.com/content/c46f767c-c8e3-47cf-b0a3-46d3b84498c3', 'https://www.ft.com/content/c3759294-57c1-4716-8b8f-48b16b818c21']",[],"[{'id': '8c8ac6be268b4386a6e3d9a61481b4c9', 'name': 'Chris Nuttall'}]",,,"[{'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.07960049}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07902207}, {'name': '10 per cent', 'weight': 0.06260354}, {'name': '2 per cent', 'weight': 0.06260354}, {'name': '22 per cent', 'weight': 0.06260354}, {'name': '4 per cent', 'weight': 0.06260354}, {'name': '51 per cent', 'weight': 0.06260354}, {'name': '6 per cent', 'weight': 0.06260354}, {'name': '9 per cent', 'weight': 0.06260354}, {'name': 'MX Mechanical Mini', 'weight': 0.056696}]",[],[{'name': 'Tech'}],"[{'data': 'Snap', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Twitter', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Alphabet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Pinterest', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Morgan Stanley', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gartner', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Canalys', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Spotify', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Peloton', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Meituan', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Money Clinic', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Logitech', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'overnight', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Evan Spiegel', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Andy Jassy', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Do Kwon', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Cristina Criddle', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Beijing', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'S Korea', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Madeira', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ponta do Sol', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukrainian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Portuguese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Master Series', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MX Mechanical', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'MX Master 3S', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tactile Quiet', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Clicky', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Linear', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mini', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': '2069a416008f4285bd8daaaf03071360', 'name': 'Amazon Robotics', 'domains': ['amazonrobotics.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '8caf38e313df456e9308f2d5341b0253', 'name': 'Meituan', 'domains': ['about.meituan.com'], 'symbols': ['3690.HK', 'MPNGY']}, {'id': '2c3d7e5ad5794137b758c59364adddd5', 'name': 'Snap Inc.', 'domains': ['snap.com'], 'symbols': ['1SI.DE', 'SNAP']}, {'id': 'd27f0b8208714a54aca577fca7595288', 'name': 'Logitech International S.A.', 'domains': ['logitech.com'], 'symbols': ['LOGI', 'LOGN.SW']}]","{'positive': 0.0070917984, 'negative': 0.9753214, 'neutral': 0.017586688}","Snap has seen its shares fall 40% due to a rapid deterioration in the “macroeconomic environment” over the past month, with Twitter, Alphabet, Meta 9% and Pinterest 22%. Snap's CEO Evan Spiegel said the company faced “rising inflation and interest rates, supply chain shortages and labour disruptions, platform policy changes, the impact of the war in Ukraine and more” as well as factors such as “delayed product launches due to ongoing component shortages, rising inflation and poor consumer confidence” The Internet of (Five) Things, Amazon's annual ear-bashing, and Airbnb's China exit are among the things to be challenged.",,[],False,79bec1cf7a314673b86f26a36de08490,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q41812531', 'name': 'Andy Jassy'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q55728246', 'name': 'Ha Do-kwon'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q15439301', 'name': 'Evan Spiegel'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/f2fa28da-ef50-41c8-aadf-0a384f9ee47f,,9ed9ee03eade4ac894ca71eec15c12f0,46ec238645544e95ac783aa61d87b316,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F6d1ef6f8-8031-449b-a2a2-a84c991bc945.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-24T09:38:40.377000+00:00,2022-05-24T09:38:40.377000+00:00,2022-05-24T09:38:40.377000+00:00,2.0,Airbnb/China: exit leaves fat margins to local rivals,Competitors such as Meituan are well-placed to benefit from demand when lockdowns ease,Another US tech group is biting the dust in China. Airbnb will close its business there after years of heavy investment. The room rental giant has said it is throwing in its complimentary towel becaus... [2107 symbols],Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/f491744b-10a9-4f0a-b4b5-d9d8851aff24', 'https://ep.ft.com/newsletters/56657d10e4b04e04251004fd/subscribe']",[],[],,,"[{'name': 'Airbnb', 'weight': 0.09232752}, {'name': 'food delivery', 'weight': 0.08483348}, {'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.08344344}, {'name': 'market share', 'weight': 0.0829633}, {'name': 'forward sales multiple', 'weight': 0.08184688}, {'name': 'local travel', 'weight': 0.08129944}, {'name': 'subdued travel', 'weight': 0.07648892}, {'name': 'outbound travel', 'weight': 0.0759836}, {'name': 'Chinese tourists', 'weight': 0.07561737}, {'name': 'Chinese authorities', 'weight': 0.07260287}]","[{'name': 'Airbnb'}, {'name': 'China'}]",[{'name': 'Travel'}],"[{'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Tujia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Xiaozhu', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meituan', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Beijing', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 3}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': '8caf38e313df456e9308f2d5341b0253', 'name': 'Meituan', 'domains': ['about.meituan.com'], 'symbols': ['3690.HK', 'MPNGY']}]","{'positive': 0.027967252, 'negative': 0.94811106, 'neutral': 0.023921654}","Airbnb has announced that it will close its business in China due to the country's “zero-Covid” policy. The withdrawal will help local rivals in the fiercely competitive market, and Meituan, which launched its own room rental platform in 2017, could benefit from surging demand when lockdowns ease. However, revenues from the accommodation and travel unit grew more than 50 per cent last year, while operating margins for accommodation have hit more than 43 per cent compared with just 6 per cent for food delivery.",,[],False,628d0e840c59453b8e99827d284e608c,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/527a777a-f19c-4480-af9f-289b9af250d5,Alice Hancock,4a436708924f4ff495faabb6b14a6cc8,c58578e41f5642859c5a6144c5d2dc04,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2Ffe3e41f2-cffd-4e0e-8487-960ea2bbc064.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-05-21T10:00:16.367000+00:00,2022-05-21T10:00:16.367000+00:00,2022-05-21T10:00:16.367000+00:00,2.0,Holiday let companies rush to sign up properties ahead of summer,Hoseasons and Vrbo among brands preparing for higher demand this year after supply of homes fell during pandemic,"Vacation rental companies are scrambling to secure accommodation as a burst of pent-up summer demand and a drop in the number of holiday lets during the pandemic prompts fears of a supply squeeze.

He... [3590 symbols]",Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/278c8e52-9b48-412c-af71-383b8bd60e80', 'https://www.ft.com/content/af56e921-501d-4860-8e1a-75f0652177cf']",[],"[{'id': '1d064328b7a441b3b50c410591e64000', 'name': 'Alice Hancock'}]",,,"[{'name': 'last year', 'weight': 0.0900985}, {'name': 'August last year', 'weight': 0.08948609}, {'name': 'holiday lets', 'weight': 0.084749155}, {'name': 'year', 'weight': 0.07160471}, {'name': 'Holiday let companies', 'weight': 0.07053895}, {'name': 'holidays', 'weight': 0.0687553}, {'name': 'last December', 'weight': 0.06823162}, {'name': 'Plum Guide', 'weight': 0.067200124}, {'name': 'available properties', 'weight': 0.064886525}, {'name': 'city centre offices', 'weight': 0.06213542}]",[],[{'name': 'Business'}],"[{'data': 'Henrik Kjellberg', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Doron Meyassed', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Graham Donoghue', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Awaze', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Hoseasons', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cottages.com', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Expedia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vrbo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Plum Guide', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Transparent', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AirDNA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Italy', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Portugal', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mediterranean', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the last minute', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': 'dcf399bec455474e97819435f374b218', 'name': 'Expedia Group Inc', 'domains': ['expediainc.com'], 'symbols': ['E3X1.DE']}]","{'positive': 0.056466114, 'negative': 0.9059928, 'neutral': 0.03754115}","Vacation rental companies are scrambling to secure accommodation due to pent-up demand and a drop in the number of holiday lets during the pandemic. Awaze has added 6,000 new holiday lets so far this year to its websites, almost 40 per cent more than during the same period in 2019. Expedia-owned holiday rental company Vrbo said demand for summer was 15 per cent ahead of the same point last year and many “top locations” were already sold out. Tighter regulation of short-term rental accommodation, particularly in cities, has also quelled the growth of available properties. Meanwhile, Airbnb this month announced an overhaul of its platform to push guests to more unusual locations. Non-urban listings had increased by 15% globally year on year in the first quarter, while Plum Guide’s Meyassed said occupancy for the next 90 days was higher than pre-Covid almost everywhere they operate.",,[],False,11f4ac784e55480c85effde61c6a4ffc,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/72a1eb6f-f1e2-4268-8ce2-9c9aa0d9bed0,Thomas Hale,beece8acc0f2460b80b61a46b4e6443c,b0f1db75947140bb9b942d2e5d0383c4,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F62415252-8fbb-4d97-ad33-ef2b3c84401c.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-06-20T02:00:49.108000+00:00,2022-06-20T02:00:49.108000+00:00,2022-06-20T02:00:49.108000+00:00,2.0,International investors cash in on China’s pension market,Reforms to develop individual private pensions for the country’s ageing population have created a wealth of opportunities for the world’s biggest asset managers,"As China’s age profile continues its rapid inversion, the need for more private pensions is drawing some of the biggest asset managers to the world’s most populous nation.

These so-called Pillar III ... [5662 symbols]",Article,['https://www.ft.com/content/f491744b-10a9-4f0a-b4b5-d9d8851aff24'],[],"[{'id': '0f2f7919636e4932860fb3812c8be6db', 'name': 'Thomas Hale'}]",,,"[{'name': 'China', 'weight': 0.08632233}, {'name': 'Greater China', 'weight': 0.08574445}, {'name': 'China Construction Bank', 'weight': 0.085460454}, {'name': 'pension reforms', 'weight': 0.08296021}, {'name': 'individual private pensions', 'weight': 0.08046496}, {'name': 'private pension schemes', 'weight': 0.0798589}, {'name': 'third pillar pensions', 'weight': 0.0792323}, {'name': 'second pillar pensions', 'weight': 0.076210454}, {'name': 'China’s pension market', 'weight': 0.06360039}, {'name': 'China’s pension reform', 'weight': 0.06300086}]",[{'name': 'China'}],[],"[{'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 14}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Shanghai', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Canada', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chile', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BlackRock', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'the People’s Bank of China', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'China Construction Bank', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Goldman Sachs Asset Management', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ICBC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amundi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the University of Adelaide', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Z-Ben Advisors', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Omicron', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Congress', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Susan Chan', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Larry Fink', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Liu He', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Xi Jinping', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lauren Johnston', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Peter Alexander', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Asia Pacific', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 2}]","[{'id': '0865d91839f74de6853cee4406e08fcb', 'name': 'China Construction Bank Corporation', 'domains': ['ccb.com'], 'symbols': ['0939.HK', '601939.SS', 'CICHY']}, {'id': '3e2ec86789e14d8c8948de521c314f00', 'name': 'Amundi', 'domains': ['legroupe.amundi.com'], 'symbols': ['AMUN.PA']}, {'id': '68678be26e61415981da7ec3a469b40c', 'name': 'China Investment and Finance Group Limited', 'domains': ['garroninternational.com'], 'symbols': ['1226.HK']}, {'id': '82f01e7bd8d54c41abad873e37433e98', 'name': 'Industrial and Commercial Bank of China (Asia)', 'domains': ['icbcasia.com'], 'symbols': []}, {'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}, {'id': '89ed83fe779b47909391279deb7c66e3', 'name': 'BlackRock, Inc.', 'domains': ['blackrock.com'], 'symbols': ['0QZZ.L', 'BLK', 'BLK.SW', 'BLQA.DE']}, {'id': '5fd4e230ce83489ba4aa19dc2cc39c7a', 'name': 'Central Bank of the Republic of China', 'domains': ['cbc.gov.tw'], 'symbols': []}]","{'positive': 0.5655775, 'negative': 0.015145903, 'neutral': 0.4192766}","As China's age profile continues its rapid inversion, the need for more private pensions is drawing some of the world's biggest asset managers to the world’s most populous nation. This year, a 2020 study produced by BlackRock and the People's Bank of China found that only Rmb2.2tn ($330bn) had been invested in them, highlighting the relatively low amount of savings in the country's private pension system. In April, Chinese authorities unveiled long-awaited measures that pave the way for the greater development of individual private pensions in a country where savings are still dominated by cash and real estate. Other international firms that have recently gained approvals in China include Goldman Sachs Asset Management, which in 2021 partnered with China's biggest bank, ICBC, and Europe's largest asset manager Amundi. The government may also hope that it will have the capacity to “cross-subsidise” the existing government pension system, while significant, hint at a move gradual approach to pension reforms.",,[],False,94e30c7afe5b4661aef52c5b3f49ccd2,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q3218882', 'name': 'Larry Fink'}, {'wikidataId': 'Q15031', 'name': 'Xi Jinping'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/cf04b419-dc1c-4752-aa71-2dd2857d549b,Charles Calkin,9c99e7a14c6a444d8f43bcbf7470d631,5bf126b1b1bf45daa942330df64153c7,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F2e814bf4-1a93-4dc5-a0c4-f32fb6145331.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-06-22T04:00:05.755000+00:00,2022-06-22T04:00:05.755000+00:00,2022-06-22T04:00:05.755000+00:00,2.0,Frozen tax allowances and inflation chill investors,What should you do during the fiscal ice age?,Over the past few years one of the biggest concerns for many of our clients has been the danger of the government introducing a wealth tax. Today many of us face an even greater threat — tax by stealt... [6044 symbols],Article,"['https://www.ft.com/content/1ea04835-4837-43fb-a321-2dcc97539a55', 'https://www.ft.com/content/6dea82f3-59ea-4736-a0db-b808f08bab6a', 'https://www.ft.com/content/7a1d657a-c7d4-47b1-8bc9-03b5a0a47bdf']",[],"[{'id': None, 'name': 'Charles Calkin'}]",,,"[{'name': 'several years', 'weight': 0.08724582}, {'name': 'existing tax allowances', 'weight': 0.08335716}, {'name': 'Frozen tax allowances', 'weight': 0.08226093}, {'name': 'cash savings', 'weight': 0.078055196}, {'name': 'inflation', 'weight': 0.07115678}, {'name': 'Income tax thresholds', 'weight': 0.0707866}, {'name': 'allowances', 'weight': 0.06682104}, {'name': 'tax', 'weight': 0.06590536}, {'name': 'inheritance tax', 'weight': 0.064364575}, {'name': 'pension contribution limits', 'weight': 0.06199636}]",[{'name': 'Inflation'}],[{'name': 'Politics'}],"[{'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'James Hambro & Partners', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Charles Calkin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.07219357, 'negative': 0.40109354, 'neutral': 0.5267129}","Over the past few years, many of our clients have been concerned about introducing a wealth tax due to inflation and rising house prices. Nearly all the core tax allowances have been frozen, and inflation is forecast to breach 11% by October. The pension lifetime allowance and inheritance tax thresholds have all been frozen in line with inflation, and the residence nil-rate band threshold has been frozen at £175,000 since 2020-21. This could mean an additional tax charge of over £33,000 for those breaching the limits and taking the surplus in cash. If you are retired and can afford it, consider drawing more heavily from your general investment accounts and Isas than your pensions.",,[],False,fdd6f67e2fd84ad69d3b0654f49b460a,[],[],ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/d94695dc-f826-403b-a154-b8fe7b77856e,Oliver Barnes,b78a499e89ea4d4695d97fc9a80407af,5ad7d0d4d1ac418a8c9e7006fc8ae4da,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F0982b403-d218-4a1f-a8fc-45dfdf852a95.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-06-28T23:08:57.675000+00:00,2022-06-28T23:08:57.675000+00:00,2022-06-28T23:08:57.675000+00:00,2.0,Short-term lets face stricter rules as review gauges impact on tourist hotspots,Concern over proliferation of Airbnb-style rentals in popular holiday destinations spurs action,Curbs on Airbnb-style rental properties in England are being proposed by the UK government as part of a review aimed at reducing the negative impact of short-term holiday lets on residents and the hou... [3661 symbols],Article,['https://www.ft.com/content/e619d613-6d4a-4bfb-8d97-1e544362ec96'],[],"[{'id': '62de2376933e487a87c95a7a49779af1', 'name': 'Oliver Barnes'}]",,,"[{'name': 'housing supply', 'weight': 0.08278103}, {'name': 'housing supply problems', 'weight': 0.082502976}, {'name': 'rented housing supply', 'weight': 0.08078838}, {'name': 'housing minister', 'weight': 0.07789303}, {'name': 'Airbnb rentals', 'weight': 0.07335845}, {'name': 'stricter rules', 'weight': 0.06760119}, {'name': 'rule breakers', 'weight': 0.066871785}, {'name': 'tourist hotspots', 'weight': 0.06533179}, {'name': 'holiday rental options', 'weight': 0.06519071}, {'name': 'short-term holiday lets', 'weight': 0.06512353}]",[],[{'name': 'Travel'}],"[{'data': 'England', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'UK', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Amsterdam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Paris', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Scotland', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Northern Ireland', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Airbnb', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Westminster', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Short Term Accommodation Association', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the National Residential Landlords Association', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the 2015', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stuart Andrew', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Merilee Karr', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ben Beadle', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Welsh', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}]","[{'id': '90a28a5603a64095a5595b107fbafa14', 'name': 'Airbnb, Inc.', 'domains': ['airbnb.com'], 'symbols': ['ABNB']}]","{'positive': 0.055705223, 'negative': 0.45118195, 'neutral': 0.4931128}","The UK government is proposing a review to reduce the negative impact of short-term holiday lets on residents and the housing market in tourist hotspots. The review, which will last for three months, will also re-examine provisions outlined in the 2015 deregulation act, which relaxed the rules on short term lets in London. The Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport acknowledged the “many benefits” brought by such lets, including increasing holiday rental options and allowing people to make money from spare rooms and second homes. However, Ben Beadle, chief executive of the National Residential Landlords Association, said the suggested policies “would be unlikely to remedy” housing supply problems.",,[],False,8e10a1f8b2164f50917d6213d0b28ba9,[],"[{'wikidataId': 'Q259707', 'name': 'Stuart Andrew'}]",ABNB,,,
https://www.ft.com/content/71345e19-c06e-47e7-a63d-47cf76ed98ff,Patrick McGee,70e10b4272d54308a4113014b2f33775,6fb8a0d888fb452084cc497992c68dd8,"{'domain': 'ft.com', 'paywall': True, 'location': None}",https://www.ft.com/__origami/service/image/v2/images/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2Fa8f77cff-7b83-4ccd-8bb4-8e204dbe712a.jpg?source=next-opengraph&fit=scale-down&width=900,gb,en,2022-07-22T18:31:53.574000+00:00,2022-07-22T18:31:53.574000+00:00,2022-07-22T18:31:53.574000+00:00,2.0,Airbnb hires former White House press secretary Jay Carney from Amazon,Departure marks the latest in a number of recent exits from the ecommerce group,"Former White House press secretary Jay Carney is joining Airbnb to head policy and communications, following a seven-year stint at Amazon where he led the lobbying and media relations team.
