summary,title,pubDate,addDate,n_companies,authorsByline,source,companies,entities,positive_sentiment,negative_sentiment,neutral_sentiment,open,close,ticker
"BlackRock has launched a thematic equity fund called the Global Metaverse & Virtual Interaction Select Index, which selects constituents from a wide range of stocks from developed and emerging markets. The fund will go towards companies that contribute in the development of virtual platforms, gaming, 3D software, digital assets, and virtual and augmented reality. Microsoft recently ended its project to encourage the use of the metaverse in industrial environments, but BlackRock still sees potential in the concept and is positioning itself accordingly. BlackRock predicts that bond ETF assets industry-wide will more than double to $5 trillion in 2030.",Apple is planning new VR lens tech,2022-03-03,2022-03-03,1,Michelle D. Madsen,[{'domain': 'metanews.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'BlackRock', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'ETF Strategy', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Morningstar', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Global Equity Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Meta Platforms', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Netease', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Roblox', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'KPMG', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'iShares', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'James Lord', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Neal Stephenson', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mark Zuckerberg', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Laurence Fink', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}]",0.06747531,0.012582644,0.919942,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"The US has strengthened its cyber defences in the Ukraine conflict, as well as the lower tempo, intensity and sophistication of what Russian-government hackers are known to be capable of. The US had been helping Ukraine for months before the invasion to identify and prepare for possible cyber attacks. The UK is to clamp down on online scams and “unlicensed financial promotions” as it expands plans to restrict what people can post on the internet. China has cut Russian smartphone shipments and Chinese brands are set to be hit hard by sanctions. US media tycoon Barry Diller and music mogul David Geffen are under investigation for potential insider trading connected to the purchase of Activision Blizzard options. Amazon is accused of obstructing its investigation.",US strengthens Ukraine’s cyber defences,2022-03-09,2022-03-09,5,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Activision Publishing', 'symbols': []}","[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Romania', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Californian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukrainian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Ukrainian Railways’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Fortinet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Xiaomi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oppo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Activision', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Department of Justice', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Securities and Exchange Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SEC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Congress', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'House Judiciary committee', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gillian Tett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Robin Wigglesworth', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Diller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'David Geffen', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Merrick Garland', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Patrick McGee', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Online Safety Bill', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Mac Studio', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'M1 Max', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ultra', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Studio Display —', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.018021135,0.93429047,0.047688473,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"The US has strengthened its cyber defences in the Ukraine conflict, as well as the lower tempo, intensity and sophistication of what Russian-government hackers are known to be capable of. The US had been helping Ukraine for months before the invasion to identify and prepare for possible cyber attacks. The UK is to clamp down on online scams and “unlicensed financial promotions” as it expands plans to restrict what people can post on the internet. China has cut Russian smartphone shipments and Chinese brands are set to be hit hard by sanctions. US media tycoon Barry Diller and music mogul David Geffen are under investigation for potential insider trading connected to the purchase of Activision Blizzard options. Amazon is accused of obstructing its investigation.",US strengthens Ukraine’s cyber defences,2022-03-09,2022-03-09,5,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Amazon Robotics', 'symbols': []}","[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Romania', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Californian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukrainian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Ukrainian Railways’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Fortinet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Xiaomi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oppo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Activision', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Department of Justice', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Securities and Exchange Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SEC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Congress', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'House Judiciary committee', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gillian Tett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Robin Wigglesworth', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Diller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'David Geffen', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Merrick Garland', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Patrick McGee', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Online Safety Bill', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Mac Studio', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'M1 Max', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ultra', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Studio Display —', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.018021135,0.93429047,0.047688473,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"The US has strengthened its cyber defences in the Ukraine conflict, as well as the lower tempo, intensity and sophistication of what Russian-government hackers are known to be capable of. The US had been helping Ukraine for months before the invasion to identify and prepare for possible cyber attacks. The UK is to clamp down on online scams and “unlicensed financial promotions” as it expands plans to restrict what people can post on the internet. China has cut Russian smartphone shipments and Chinese brands are set to be hit hard by sanctions. US media tycoon Barry Diller and music mogul David Geffen are under investigation for potential insider trading connected to the purchase of Activision Blizzard options. Amazon is accused of obstructing its investigation.",US strengthens Ukraine’s cyber defences,2022-03-09,2022-03-09,5,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Romania', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Californian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukrainian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Ukrainian Railways’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Fortinet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Xiaomi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oppo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Activision', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Department of Justice', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Securities and Exchange Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SEC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Congress', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'House Judiciary committee', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gillian Tett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Robin Wigglesworth', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Diller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'David Geffen', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Merrick Garland', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Patrick McGee', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Online Safety Bill', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Mac Studio', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'M1 Max', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ultra', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Studio Display —', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.018021135,0.93429047,0.047688473,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"The US has strengthened its cyber defences in the Ukraine conflict, as well as the lower tempo, intensity and sophistication of what Russian-government hackers are known to be capable of. The US had been helping Ukraine for months before the invasion to identify and prepare for possible cyber attacks. The UK is to clamp down on online scams and “unlicensed financial promotions” as it expands plans to restrict what people can post on the internet. China has cut Russian smartphone shipments and Chinese brands are set to be hit hard by sanctions. US media tycoon Barry Diller and music mogul David Geffen are under investigation for potential insider trading connected to the purchase of Activision Blizzard options. Amazon is accused of obstructing its investigation.",US strengthens Ukraine’s cyber defences,2022-03-09,2022-03-09,5,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Activision Blizzard Inc', 'symbols': ['AIY.DE']}","[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Romania', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Californian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukrainian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Ukrainian Railways’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Fortinet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Xiaomi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oppo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Activision', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Department of Justice', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Securities and Exchange Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SEC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Congress', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'House Judiciary committee', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gillian Tett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Robin Wigglesworth', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Diller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'David Geffen', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Merrick Garland', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Patrick McGee', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Online Safety Bill', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Mac Studio', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'M1 Max', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ultra', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Studio Display —', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.018021135,0.93429047,0.047688473,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"The US has strengthened its cyber defences in the Ukraine conflict, as well as the lower tempo, intensity and sophistication of what Russian-government hackers are known to be capable of. The US had been helping Ukraine for months before the invasion to identify and prepare for possible cyber attacks. The UK is to clamp down on online scams and “unlicensed financial promotions” as it expands plans to restrict what people can post on the internet. China has cut Russian smartphone shipments and Chinese brands are set to be hit hard by sanctions. US media tycoon Barry Diller and music mogul David Geffen are under investigation for potential insider trading connected to the purchase of Activision Blizzard options. Amazon is accused of obstructing its investigation.",US strengthens Ukraine’s cyber defences,2022-03-09,2022-03-09,5,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Microsoft Corporation', 'symbols': ['4338.HK', 'MSF.BR', 'MSF.DE', 'MSFT']}","[{'data': 'US', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 11}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Romania', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'American', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Californian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukrainian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Ukrainian Railways’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Fortinet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Xiaomi', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oppo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Lex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nasdaq', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Activision', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Department of Justice', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Securities and Exchange Commission', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'SEC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Congress', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'House Judiciary committee', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gillian Tett', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Robin Wigglesworth', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Diller', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'David Geffen', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Merrick Garland', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Patrick McGee', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Online Safety Bill', 'type': 'LAW', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Mac Studio', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'M1 Max', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ultra', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Studio Display —', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.018021135,0.93429047,0.047688473,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"Sequoia Capital's John Sutter argues that Institutional Shareholder Services, the largest of the firms offering advice to fund managers and investors about how to vote on issues at annual shareholder meetings, should not be judge and jury. He argues that ISS's influence has grown for several reasons, including the size and structure of Apple CEO Tim Cook's $99mn pay and bonuses package for 2021, and its influence was shown in the vote against the board’s pay recommendation. ISS also operates a ballot vote counting service and provides research for class action stockholder lawsuits. Companies should recruit directors willing to ignore browbeating and who structure pay packages for executives that reward them handsomely for spectacular performance, and investors and fund managers should discard their crutches and stand tall.",Tim Cook pay vote shows ISS should not be judge and jury,2022-03-09,2022-03-09,2,Michael Moritz,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'Tim Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'ISS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 12}, {'data': 'Sequoia Capital', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Institutional Shareholder Services', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Glass Lewis', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Moody’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Fitch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}]",0.042381383,0.07848599,0.8791326,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"Sequoia Capital's John Sutter argues that Institutional Shareholder Services, the largest of the firms offering advice to fund managers and investors about how to vote on issues at annual shareholder meetings, should not be judge and jury. He argues that ISS's influence has grown for several reasons, including the size and structure of Apple CEO Tim Cook's $99mn pay and bonuses package for 2021, and its influence was shown in the vote against the board’s pay recommendation. ISS also operates a ballot vote counting service and provides research for class action stockholder lawsuits. Companies should recruit directors willing to ignore browbeating and who structure pay packages for executives that reward them handsomely for spectacular performance, and investors and fund managers should discard their crutches and stand tall.",Tim Cook pay vote shows ISS should not be judge and jury,2022-03-09,2022-03-09,2,Michael Moritz,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'ISS A/S', 'symbols': ['ISS.CO', 'ISSDY']}","[{'data': 'Tim Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'ISS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 12}, {'data': 'Sequoia Capital', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Institutional Shareholder Services', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Glass Lewis', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Moody’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Fitch', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'America', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}]",0.042381383,0.07848599,0.8791326,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"Apple has become a major player in the tech industry due to the technical performance of its in-house chips. These include Google’s AI processors, Amazon Web Services’ Graviton data centre chips, and Google's TPUs. Apple has been able to integrate chip design into its wider technology development plans, which could give them an edge in self-driving cars and augmented reality products. Google recently gave a glimpse into the many advantages that come from chip design, spelling out 10 lessons it has learnt from building its TPU's since 2015.",Big Tech raises its bets on chips,2022-03-10,2022-03-10,4,Richard Waters,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Alphabet Inc.', 'symbols': ['ABEA.DE', 'ABEC.DE', 'GOOG', 'GOOGL', 'GOOGL.SW']}","[{'data': 'Steve Jobs', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Amazon Web Services’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TSMC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AWS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Annapurna', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'iPad', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mac', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Graviton', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'X86', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Trainium', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.17895535,0.015096758,0.8059479,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"Apple has become a major player in the tech industry due to the technical performance of its in-house chips. These include Google’s AI processors, Amazon Web Services’ Graviton data centre chips, and Google's TPUs. Apple has been able to integrate chip design into its wider technology development plans, which could give them an edge in self-driving cars and augmented reality products. Google recently gave a glimpse into the many advantages that come from chip design, spelling out 10 lessons it has learnt from building its TPU's since 2015.",Big Tech raises its bets on chips,2022-03-10,2022-03-10,4,Richard Waters,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'NVIDIA Corporation', 'symbols': ['NVD.DE', 'NVDA']}","[{'data': 'Steve Jobs', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Amazon Web Services’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TSMC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AWS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Annapurna', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'iPad', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mac', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Graviton', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'X86', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Trainium', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.17895535,0.015096758,0.8059479,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"Apple has become a major player in the tech industry due to the technical performance of its in-house chips. These include Google’s AI processors, Amazon Web Services’ Graviton data centre chips, and Google's TPUs. Apple has been able to integrate chip design into its wider technology development plans, which could give them an edge in self-driving cars and augmented reality products. Google recently gave a glimpse into the many advantages that come from chip design, spelling out 10 lessons it has learnt from building its TPU's since 2015.",Big Tech raises its bets on chips,2022-03-10,2022-03-10,4,Richard Waters,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Big Apple Donuts and Coffee', 'symbols': []}","[{'data': 'Steve Jobs', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Amazon Web Services’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TSMC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AWS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Annapurna', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'iPad', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mac', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Graviton', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'X86', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Trainium', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.17895535,0.015096758,0.8059479,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"Apple has become a major player in the tech industry due to the technical performance of its in-house chips. These include Google’s AI processors, Amazon Web Services’ Graviton data centre chips, and Google's TPUs. Apple has been able to integrate chip design into its wider technology development plans, which could give them an edge in self-driving cars and augmented reality products. Google recently gave a glimpse into the many advantages that come from chip design, spelling out 10 lessons it has learnt from building its TPU's since 2015.",Big Tech raises its bets on chips,2022-03-10,2022-03-10,4,Richard Waters,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'Steve Jobs', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Amazon Web Services’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tesla', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TSMC', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AWS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Annapurna', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nvidia', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'iPad', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mac', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Graviton', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Arm', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'X86', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Trainium', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.17895535,0.015096758,0.8059479,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"Apple has suspended sales of its products in Russia due to the country's government's anti-disinformation campaign. The move follows a similar move by Google, Facebook, YouTube and TikTok. Ford has announced plans to increase electric sales targets and Netflix has swooped in to buy Next Games, extending Silicon Valley’s push into video games. Meanwhile, Huawei has unveiled its Mate X and Mate Book for its e ink screen and stylus.",Apple’s Russian withdrawal,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,7,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palantir', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NHS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Next Games', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ericsson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Finnish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swedish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Iraq', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Tokyo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'the MatePad Paper', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M-Pencil', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the MateBook X Pro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'i7', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MateStation X', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PixLab X1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sound Joy', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Bradshaw', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Madhumita Murgia', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Leo Lewis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley’s', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stranger Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mobile World Congress', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.010662383,0.91227436,0.077063315,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"Apple has suspended sales of its products in Russia due to the country's government's anti-disinformation campaign. The move follows a similar move by Google, Facebook, YouTube and TikTok. Ford has announced plans to increase electric sales targets and Netflix has swooped in to buy Next Games, extending Silicon Valley’s push into video games. Meanwhile, Huawei has unveiled its Mate X and Mate Book for its e ink screen and stylus.",Apple’s Russian withdrawal,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,7,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Netflix, Inc.', 'symbols': ['NFC.DE', 'NFLX']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palantir', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NHS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Next Games', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ericsson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Finnish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swedish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Iraq', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Tokyo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'the MatePad Paper', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M-Pencil', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the MateBook X Pro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'i7', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MateStation X', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PixLab X1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sound Joy', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Bradshaw', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Madhumita Murgia', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Leo Lewis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley’s', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stranger Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mobile World Congress', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.010662383,0.91227436,0.077063315,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"Apple has suspended sales of its products in Russia due to the country's government's anti-disinformation campaign. The move follows a similar move by Google, Facebook, YouTube and TikTok. Ford has announced plans to increase electric sales targets and Netflix has swooped in to buy Next Games, extending Silicon Valley’s push into video games. Meanwhile, Huawei has unveiled its Mate X and Mate Book for its e ink screen and stylus.",Apple’s Russian withdrawal,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,7,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Telefonaktiebolaget LM Ericsson (publ)', 'symbols': ['ERCB.DE', 'ERCG.DE', 'ERIBR.HE', 'ERIC', 'ERIC-A.ST', 'ERIC-B.ST']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palantir', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NHS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Next Games', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ericsson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Finnish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swedish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Iraq', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Tokyo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'the MatePad Paper', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M-Pencil', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the MateBook X Pro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'i7', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MateStation X', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PixLab X1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sound Joy', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Bradshaw', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Madhumita Murgia', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Leo Lewis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley’s', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stranger Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mobile World Congress', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.010662383,0.91227436,0.077063315,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"Apple has suspended sales of its products in Russia due to the country's government's anti-disinformation campaign. The move follows a similar move by Google, Facebook, YouTube and TikTok. Ford has announced plans to increase electric sales targets and Netflix has swooped in to buy Next Games, extending Silicon Valley’s push into video games. Meanwhile, Huawei has unveiled its Mate X and Mate Book for its e ink screen and stylus.",Apple’s Russian withdrawal,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,7,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Ford Motor Company', 'symbols': ['F', 'FMC1.DE']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palantir', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NHS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Next Games', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ericsson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Finnish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swedish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Iraq', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Tokyo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'the MatePad Paper', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M-Pencil', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the MateBook X Pro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'i7', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MateStation X', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PixLab X1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sound Joy', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Bradshaw', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Madhumita Murgia', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Leo Lewis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley’s', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stranger Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mobile World Congress', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.010662383,0.91227436,0.077063315,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"Apple has suspended sales of its products in Russia due to the country's government's anti-disinformation campaign. The move follows a similar move by Google, Facebook, YouTube and TikTok. Ford has announced plans to increase electric sales targets and Netflix has swooped in to buy Next Games, extending Silicon Valley’s push into video games. Meanwhile, Huawei has unveiled its Mate X and Mate Book for its e ink screen and stylus.",Apple’s Russian withdrawal,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,7,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Palantir Technologies Inc.', 'symbols': ['PLTR']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palantir', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NHS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Next Games', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ericsson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Finnish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swedish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Iraq', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Tokyo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'the MatePad Paper', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M-Pencil', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the MateBook X Pro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'i7', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MateStation X', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PixLab X1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sound Joy', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Bradshaw', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Madhumita Murgia', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Leo Lewis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley’s', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stranger Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mobile World Congress', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.010662383,0.91227436,0.077063315,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"Apple has suspended sales of its products in Russia due to the country's government's anti-disinformation campaign. The move follows a similar move by Google, Facebook, YouTube and TikTok. Ford has announced plans to increase electric sales targets and Netflix has swooped in to buy Next Games, extending Silicon Valley’s push into video games. Meanwhile, Huawei has unveiled its Mate X and Mate Book for its e ink screen and stylus.",Apple’s Russian withdrawal,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,7,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Huawei', 'symbols': []}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palantir', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NHS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Next Games', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ericsson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Finnish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swedish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Iraq', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Tokyo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'the MatePad Paper', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M-Pencil', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the MateBook X Pro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'i7', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MateStation X', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PixLab X1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sound Joy', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Bradshaw', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Madhumita Murgia', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Leo Lewis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley’s', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stranger Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mobile World Congress', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.010662383,0.91227436,0.077063315,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"Apple has suspended sales of its products in Russia due to the country's government's anti-disinformation campaign. The move follows a similar move by Google, Facebook, YouTube and TikTok. Ford has announced plans to increase electric sales targets and Netflix has swooped in to buy Next Games, extending Silicon Valley’s push into video games. Meanwhile, Huawei has unveiled its Mate X and Mate Book for its e ink screen and stylus.",Apple’s Russian withdrawal,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,7,Chris Nuttall,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Alphabet Inc.', 'symbols': ['ABEA.DE', 'ABEC.DE', 'GOOG', 'GOOGL', 'GOOGL.SW']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 10}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Palantir', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'NHS', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Netflix', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Next Games', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ericsson', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Huawei', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Finnish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swedish', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 8}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Iraq', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Japan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Tokyo', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Barcelona', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'the MatePad Paper', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M-Pencil', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the MateBook X Pro', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'i7', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MateStation X', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PixLab X1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sound Joy', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Bradshaw', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Madhumita Murgia', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Leo Lewis', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley’s', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Stranger Things', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mobile World Congress', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.010662383,0.91227436,0.077063315,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"Apple on Tuesday announced the launch of a high-end desktop computer that would leverage its successful homegrown M1 chips. The Mac Studio, starting at $1,999, is akin to a pro version of Mac Mini and connects to an external monitor. It comes as Apple looks to gain an iPhone-like market share in the desktop segment following the success of the M1 chip, the company’s first desktop processor. Apple also announced the revamped the iPhone SE, first released in 2016 and refreshed in 2020. With a starting price of $429, it is intended to lure Android users without cannibalising potential buyers of higher-margin iPhones.",Apple launches high-end PC in drive to leverage homegrown chips,2022-03-08,2022-03-08,1,Patrick McGee,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'Intel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Samsung', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gartner', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'CCS Insight', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Android', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Creative Strategies', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'M1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'The Mac Studio', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'iPhone', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Ultra', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '5', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'A15 Bionic', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ben Wood', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Carolina Milanesi', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': '5G', 'type': 'TIME', 'mentions': 1}]",0.28291592,0.034582343,0.68250173,6.862640062948326,5.007559283363937,AAPL
"Apple has suspended all product sales and access to state media outlets Russia Today and Sputnik from the iPhone’s App Store outside the country. Other US brands, such as Walt Disney, Warner Bros, and Nike, have also pulled out of operations in the region. The moves underscore how western companies are shifting focus from operational concerns associated with the Ukraine invasion to questions about the reputational risks associated with business as usual. Apple has also stopped exporting products to Russia last week and followed Google Maps in disabling live traffic updates on its mapping app in Ukraine. The Federal Security Service (FSB), which oversees all imports of Russian technology, is required to notify the Russian security agency.",Apple joins companies pulling back from Russia over Ukraine attack,2022-03-01,2022-03-01,2,"Tim Bradshaw, Andrew Edgecliffe-Johnson, Patrick McGee",[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 12}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'App Store', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Boeing', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walt Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Warner Bros', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AlixPartners', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Veracity Worldwide', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Levi Strauss', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Coca-Cola', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PepsiCo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Estée Lauder', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly-Clark', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mondelez', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Snapchat', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': '10 Downing Street', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Security Service', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FSB', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 21}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Kyiv', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Moscow', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chicago', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhone', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Secure Enclave', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'German', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swiss', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Simon Freakley', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steven Fox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Poppy Wood', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steff Chávez', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matthew Rocco', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Cold War', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",0.00905919,0.9386143,0.052326493,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"Apple has suspended all product sales and access to state media outlets Russia Today and Sputnik from the iPhone’s App Store outside the country. Other US brands, such as Walt Disney, Warner Bros, and Nike, have also pulled out of operations in the region. The moves underscore how western companies are shifting focus from operational concerns associated with the Ukraine invasion to questions about the reputational risks associated with business as usual. Apple has also stopped exporting products to Russia last week and followed Google Maps in disabling live traffic updates on its mapping app in Ukraine. The Federal Security Service (FSB), which oversees all imports of Russian technology, is required to notify the Russian security agency.",Apple joins companies pulling back from Russia over Ukraine attack,2022-03-01,2022-03-01,2,"Tim Bradshaw, Andrew Edgecliffe-Johnson, Patrick McGee",[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Snap Inc.', 'symbols': ['1SI.DE', 'SNAP']}","[{'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 12}, {'data': 'Russia Today', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Sputnik', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'App Store', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Ford', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Boeing', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walt Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Warner Bros', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'AlixPartners', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Veracity Worldwide', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Levi Strauss', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Coca-Cola', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'PepsiCo', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Estée Lauder', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kimberly-Clark', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mondelez', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Facebook', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'YouTube', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'TikTok', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Snapchat', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': '10 Downing Street', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Counterpoint Research', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Sensor Tower', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Federal Security Service', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FSB', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 21}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'Kyiv', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Moscow', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chicago', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'New York', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhone', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 5}, {'data': 'Secure Enclave', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'German', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swiss', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Simon Freakley', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steven Fox', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mykhailo Fedorov', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tim Cook', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Poppy Wood', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Steff Chávez', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Matthew Rocco', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Cold War', 'type': 'EVENT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",0.00905919,0.9386143,0.052326493,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"It is a long time since investors had to deal with a war in eastern Europe, and investors are now concerned about serious inflation. Russia and Ukraine play important roles in commodity markets, and Vladimir Putin has noted the West's lack of appetite for military action and the vulnerability of European economies to higher energy prices. Recent environmental initiatives in Europe to end investment in gas have worrying security implications, and global equity investors may come to question how dependent the companies they own are on globalised supply chains. Technology shares have been at the centre of a sell-off in global markets since last December, but their share prices are not well supported by current profits.",Investing in a time of war,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,3,Simon Edelsten,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'West', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Beijing', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Turkey', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Italy', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'European', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Germans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Vladimir Putin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Xi Jinping', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jay Powell', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nathan Rothschild’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Simon Edelsten', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Unilever', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Beiersdorf', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nivea', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Henkel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Home Depot', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Adidas', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Inditex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zara', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Roche', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Merck', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Pfizer', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the US Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Standard & Poor’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Artemis Global Select Fund', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.13689183,0.429763,0.4333452,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"It is a long time since investors had to deal with a war in eastern Europe, and investors are now concerned about serious inflation. Russia and Ukraine play important roles in commodity markets, and Vladimir Putin has noted the West's lack of appetite for military action and the vulnerability of European economies to higher energy prices. Recent environmental initiatives in Europe to end investment in gas have worrying security implications, and global equity investors may come to question how dependent the companies they own are on globalised supply chains. Technology shares have been at the centre of a sell-off in global markets since last December, but their share prices are not well supported by current profits.",Investing in a time of war,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,3,Simon Edelsten,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Unilever Philippines', 'symbols': []}","[{'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'West', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Beijing', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Turkey', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Italy', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'European', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Germans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Vladimir Putin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Xi Jinping', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jay Powell', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nathan Rothschild’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Simon Edelsten', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Unilever', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Beiersdorf', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nivea', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Henkel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Home Depot', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Adidas', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Inditex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zara', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Roche', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Merck', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Pfizer', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the US Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Standard & Poor’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Artemis Global Select Fund', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.13689183,0.429763,0.4333452,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"It is a long time since investors had to deal with a war in eastern Europe, and investors are now concerned about serious inflation. Russia and Ukraine play important roles in commodity markets, and Vladimir Putin has noted the West's lack of appetite for military action and the vulnerability of European economies to higher energy prices. Recent environmental initiatives in Europe to end investment in gas have worrying security implications, and global equity investors may come to question how dependent the companies they own are on globalised supply chains. Technology shares have been at the centre of a sell-off in global markets since last December, but their share prices are not well supported by current profits.",Investing in a time of war,2022-03-02,2022-03-02,3,Simon Edelsten,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Pfizer Limited', 'symbols': ['PFIZER.NS']}","[{'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'West', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Silicon Valley', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Beijing', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Turkey', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Italy', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'European', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Germans', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Vladimir Putin', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Xi Jinping', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Jay Powell', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nathan Rothschild’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Simon Edelsten', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Unilever', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Beiersdorf', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nivea', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Henkel', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Home Depot', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Walmart', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Adidas', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Inditex', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Zara', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Roche', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Merck', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Pfizer', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Microsoft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Amazon', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the US Federal Reserve', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Standard & Poor’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Artemis Global Select Fund', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}]",0.13689183,0.429763,0.4333452,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"The Lex newsletter argues that sanctions against Russia should go much further, as the withdrawal of western companies and imposition of sanctions amounts to a declaration of financial war against Russia. The immediate impact is uneven, with Apple's decision to stop selling products in Russia and BP's separation from its stake in Russia's state oil company Rosneft not as well as other asset divestments. The London Stock Exchange Group suspended 27 Russian companies from trading on Thursday, while China may have abstained from the UN General Assembly vote to condemn Russia for its invasion of Ukraine. The US warns that any attack by Russia's sophisticated cyber capabilities could extend beyond its borders.",The Lex Newsletter: sanctions against Russia should go much further,2022-03-04,2022-03-04,4,Elaine Moore,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'BP p.l.c.', 'symbols': ['BP', 'BP.L', 'BP.SW', 'BPE.DE', 'BPE5.DE']}","[{'data': 'The Lex Newsletter', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'CFRA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'World Semiconductor Trade Statistics', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Shell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ExxonMobil', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSCI', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FTSE Russell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rosneft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rheinmetall', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BDSV', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'EU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Polymetal International', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Refinitiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cheniere Energy’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UN General Assembly', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LastPass', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 20}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Joe Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swift', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Password1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cross-Border Interbank Payment System', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'German', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gulf Coast', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",0.024665909,0.9094535,0.06588059,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"The Lex newsletter argues that sanctions against Russia should go much further, as the withdrawal of western companies and imposition of sanctions amounts to a declaration of financial war against Russia. The immediate impact is uneven, with Apple's decision to stop selling products in Russia and BP's separation from its stake in Russia's state oil company Rosneft not as well as other asset divestments. The London Stock Exchange Group suspended 27 Russian companies from trading on Thursday, while China may have abstained from the UN General Assembly vote to condemn Russia for its invasion of Ukraine. The US warns that any attack by Russia's sophisticated cyber capabilities could extend beyond its borders.",The Lex Newsletter: sanctions against Russia should go much further,2022-03-04,2022-03-04,4,Elaine Moore,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'The Lex Newsletter', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'CFRA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'World Semiconductor Trade Statistics', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Shell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ExxonMobil', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSCI', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FTSE Russell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rosneft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rheinmetall', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BDSV', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'EU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Polymetal International', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Refinitiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cheniere Energy’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UN General Assembly', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LastPass', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 20}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Joe Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swift', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Password1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cross-Border Interbank Payment System', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'German', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gulf Coast', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",0.024665909,0.9094535,0.06588059,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"The Lex newsletter argues that sanctions against Russia should go much further, as the withdrawal of western companies and imposition of sanctions amounts to a declaration of financial war against Russia. The immediate impact is uneven, with Apple's decision to stop selling products in Russia and BP's separation from its stake in Russia's state oil company Rosneft not as well as other asset divestments. The London Stock Exchange Group suspended 27 Russian companies from trading on Thursday, while China may have abstained from the UN General Assembly vote to condemn Russia for its invasion of Ukraine. The US warns that any attack by Russia's sophisticated cyber capabilities could extend beyond its borders.",The Lex Newsletter: sanctions against Russia should go much further,2022-03-04,2022-03-04,4,Elaine Moore,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Polymetal International plc', 'symbols': ['AUCOY', 'POLY.L', 'POLY.ME']}","[{'data': 'The Lex Newsletter', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'CFRA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'World Semiconductor Trade Statistics', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Shell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ExxonMobil', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSCI', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FTSE Russell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rosneft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rheinmetall', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BDSV', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'EU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Polymetal International', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Refinitiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cheniere Energy’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UN General Assembly', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LastPass', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 20}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Joe Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swift', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Password1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cross-Border Interbank Payment System', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'German', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gulf Coast', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",0.024665909,0.9094535,0.06588059,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"The Lex newsletter argues that sanctions against Russia should go much further, as the withdrawal of western companies and imposition of sanctions amounts to a declaration of financial war against Russia. The immediate impact is uneven, with Apple's decision to stop selling products in Russia and BP's separation from its stake in Russia's state oil company Rosneft not as well as other asset divestments. The London Stock Exchange Group suspended 27 Russian companies from trading on Thursday, while China may have abstained from the UN General Assembly vote to condemn Russia for its invasion of Ukraine. The US warns that any attack by Russia's sophisticated cyber capabilities could extend beyond its borders.",The Lex Newsletter: sanctions against Russia should go much further,2022-03-04,2022-03-04,4,Elaine Moore,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Lex Mundi', 'symbols': []}","[{'data': 'The Lex Newsletter', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'CFRA', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'World Semiconductor Trade Statistics', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Nike', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Disney', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BP', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Shell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'ExxonMobil', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'MSCI', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FTSE Russell', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Rosneft', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Rheinmetall', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'BDSV', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'EU', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Polymetal International', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LSE', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Refinitiv', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cheniere Energy’s', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'UN General Assembly', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'LastPass', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 20}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Germany', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'City', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Joe Biden', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Swift', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'Password1', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Cross-Border Interbank Payment System', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 9}, {'data': 'German', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Chinese', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Europe', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Gulf Coast', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}]",0.024665909,0.9094535,0.06588059,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"When Apple suspended sales of iPhones and other products in Russia this week, it made a subtler intervention. Google and Google also turned off traffic updates for its live mapping service in Ukraine as a precaution against the invading army using it to attack. The first external sign of the invasion came when a traffic jam caused by a military column appeared on the Ukrainian border, and was spotted on Google Maps. Maps are essential in wartime, and the visual influence of data plotted on maps was illustrated powerfully elsewhere this week with the publication of new international research into the origin of the Covid-19 outbreak in Wuhan in 2019. There is a long history of nations using maps to advance their claims to imperial possession, and Russian manipulation of maps has often involved concealment and propaganda. Enormous mapping and spatial data are now available through private providers such as Apple and Google, as well as private services such as Maxar, Capella and public databases.",War in Ukraine reminds us that maps can be weapons,2022-03-04,2022-03-04,2,John Gapper,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Apple Inc.', 'symbols': ['AAPL', 'APC.DE', 'APC.F']}","[{'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kyiv', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kharkiv', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wuhan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Soho', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Philippines', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vietnam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Soviet Union', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Moscow', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Craigavon', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'County Armagh', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Financial Times’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Institute of Virology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kremlin', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'KGB', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Maxar', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Capella Space', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Planet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oligarch Jets', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Liveuamap', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukrainian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Asian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Soviet', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Dnipro river', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the South China Sea', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Huanan Seafood Wholesale Market', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'John Snow', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tamburlaine', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Christopher Marlowe’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vladimir Putin’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nikita Krushchev', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mark Monmonier', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Roman Abramovich', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oleg Deripaska', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Antonia Phinnemore', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'How to Lie with Maps', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]",0.03628214,0.30083448,0.6628834,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
"When Apple suspended sales of iPhones and other products in Russia this week, it made a subtler intervention. Google and Google also turned off traffic updates for its live mapping service in Ukraine as a precaution against the invading army using it to attack. The first external sign of the invasion came when a traffic jam caused by a military column appeared on the Ukrainian border, and was spotted on Google Maps. Maps are essential in wartime, and the visual influence of data plotted on maps was illustrated powerfully elsewhere this week with the publication of new international research into the origin of the Covid-19 outbreak in Wuhan in 2019. There is a long history of nations using maps to advance their claims to imperial possession, and Russian manipulation of maps has often involved concealment and propaganda. Enormous mapping and spatial data are now available through private providers such as Apple and Google, as well as private services such as Maxar, Capella and public databases.",War in Ukraine reminds us that maps can be weapons,2022-03-04,2022-03-04,2,John Gapper,[{'domain': 'ft.com'}],"{'name': 'Alphabet Inc.', 'symbols': ['ABEA.DE', 'ABEC.DE', 'GOOG', 'GOOGL', 'GOOGL.SW']}","[{'data': 'Ukraine', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 7}, {'data': 'Russia', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 6}, {'data': 'California', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kyiv', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kharkiv', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Wuhan', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 2}, {'data': 'China', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'London', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Soho', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Philippines', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vietnam', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'The Soviet Union', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Moscow', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Craigavon', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'County Armagh', 'type': 'GPE', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Apple', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'Google', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 3}, {'data': 'the Financial Times’', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Institute of Virology', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Kremlin', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'KGB', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Maxar', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Capella Space', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Planet', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oligarch Jets', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Liveuamap', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'FT', 'type': 'ORG', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'iPhones', 'type': 'PRODUCT', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Ukrainian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Russian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 4}, {'data': 'Asian', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Soviet', 'type': 'NORP', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Dnipro river', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the South China Sea', 'type': 'LOC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'the Huanan Seafood Wholesale Market', 'type': 'FAC', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'John Snow', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Tamburlaine', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Christopher Marlowe’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Vladimir Putin’s', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Nikita Krushchev', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Mark Monmonier', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Roman Abramovich', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Oleg Deripaska', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'Antonia Phinnemore', 'type': 'PERSON', 'mentions': 1}, {'data': 'How to Lie with Maps', 'type': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'mentions': 1}]",0.03628214,0.30083448,0.6628834,8.446017907583283,7.027936926321466,AAPL
